<events>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4506058</uri>
        <title>'Sin tax' doubles the cost of alcohol overnight in Qatar</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.01960784313725494</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Health/Addictions, dmoz/Health/Addictions/Substance Abuse, dmoz/Health/Specific Substances/Alcoholic Beverages</categories>
        <loc_country>Iran</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>25</article_count>
        <total_article_count>29</total_article_count>
        <summary>Doha is the capital of the State of Qatar.Kamran Jebreili / AP file  Qatar welcomed the new year by implementing a 100 percent tax on alcohol, doubling prices overnight and sending the cost of a 12-pack of beer jumping to $78.  The increase has been branded a "sin tax" by some residents of the wealthy Gulf state as it targets products widely prohibited under Islamic law.  It was introduced by Qatar's General Authority of Customs on Jan. 1, and applies to tobacco products, energy drinks and pork -</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4506713</uri>
        <title>'Like It Was Christmas All Year:' GOP Succeeded in Making 2018 Yet Another Year the Rich Got Richer</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.06666666666666665</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Business/Accounting, dmoz/Business/Accounting/Tax Negotiation and Representation, dmoz/Home/Personal Finance/Tax Preparation</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>89</article_count>
        <total_article_count>89</total_article_count>
        <summary>With year two of Republicans' Tax Cuts and Jobs Act (TCJA) now underway and the party touting the $1.5 trillion tax plan's supposed successes, critics of the unpopular law are spotlighting the party's broken promises and saying the so-called tax scam merely helped to make 2018 another year of bloated corporate profits and enriching the already wealthy.  In fact, the wealthy were "celebrating like it was Christmas all year, which it basically was for them," wrote Frank Clemente, executive director</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4508538</uri>
        <title>India's tariff to cost US $900m</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.09019607843137256</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Business/International Business and Trade, dmoz/Business/International Business and Trade/Import and Export, dmoz/Society/Issues/Economic</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>64</article_count>
        <total_article_count>64</total_article_count>
        <summary>Washington: India's proposed retaliatory tariffs against US agricultural products including apples, almonds and lentils will have an adverse impact on American exports worth nearly $900 million, according to the latest Congressional report.  India, in 2018, had announced higher import duties on many US products like apples, almonds, walnuts, chickpeas and lentils in retaliation to President Donald Trump's decision to impose heavy tariffs on imported steel and aluminium items, a move that sparked </summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4514562</uri>
        <title>For-Profit Chain Cancels $494 Million in Student Debt to End State Investigations</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.09019607843137245</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Business/Financial Services/College Financing, dmoz/Society/Issues/Education</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>64</article_count>
        <total_article_count>64</total_article_count>
        <summary>Nearly 180,000 former students at for-profit schools run by Career Education will not have to repay $494 million they owed to the company, a group of 49 state attorneys general announced Thursday.  The agreement to wipe out the debt held directly by Career Education, such as unpaid tuition, ended a five-year multistate investigation into complaints that the company used predatory and deceptive recruiting tactics.  Career Education misled students about the cost of its programs and its graduates' </summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4513955</uri>
        <title>Log Cabins? No, These Wooden Buildings Are High-Rises</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1843137254901961</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Business/Construction and Maintenance/Building Types, dmoz/Computers/Software/Build Management, dmoz/Business/Agriculture and Forestry/Forestry</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>7</article_count>
        <total_article_count>7</total_article_count>
        <summary>Developers have not used wood for much other than houses since the horse-and-buggy days. But the knotty building material is making a comeback.  Seeking greener projects, which many consumers continue to embrace despite an anti-environmental mood in Washington, builders are choosing timber for offices, apartments and campus buildings, rather than the concrete and steel that dominated construction for decades.  Not everybody is on board with the trend, which is playing out from coast to coast. Con</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4506134</uri>
        <title>India remains fastest growing economy ahead of China despite up/downs</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2549019607843137</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Business/Financial Services, dmoz/Society/Issues/Government Operations, dmoz/Society/Issues/Economic</categories>
        <loc_country>India</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>11</article_count>
        <total_article_count>11</total_article_count>
        <summary>NEW DELHI: India remained ahead of China to retain the tag world's fastest growing large economy withstanding several ups and downs, spike in oil prices and global trade war like situation during 2018. Indian economy's roller-coaster ride during the year gone by was best captured by the GDP growth. In the first quarter of 2018-19 ending June 30, it grew at an impressive 8.2 per cent, after 7.7 per cent in the first three months of the year.  Then it slipped to 7.1 per cent in the next quarter end</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507138</uri>
        <title>Why Modi Government is Amending the Aadhaar Act and What it Means for You</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1450980392156862</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Society/Transgendered/Law, dmoz/Business/Financial Services/Medical Billing, dmoz/Business/Telecommunications/Customer Management</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>38</article_count>
        <total_article_count>42</total_article_count>
        <summary>New Delhi: The Narendra Modi government has introduced a Bill in parliament that propose amendments to various laws that underpin the Aadhaar ecosystem, in a move that comes after a Supreme Court verdict earlier this year curtailed the sprawling nature of India's biometric authentication programme.  The Aadhaar And Other Laws (Amendment) Bill 2018, which was passed by the cabinet two weeks ago and introduced by information technology minister Ravi Shankar Prasad in the Lok Sabha on Wednesday, con</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507927</uri>
        <title>Hyundai flags tough 2019 as US, China demand stays slow</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.06666666666666665</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Home/Consumer Information/Automobiles, dmoz/Business/Marketing and Advertising/Employment, dmoz/Business/Electronics and Electrical/Electromechanical</categories>
        <loc_country>South Korea</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>37</article_count>
        <total_article_count>37</total_article_count>
        <summary>In his first New Year address to employees, group heir apparent Euisun Chung said Hyundai Motor Co and Kia Motors Corp would together launch 13 new or face-lifted models in 2019.  South Korea's Hyundai Motor Group flagged another year of tepid car sales growth on the back of a slow 2018, saying trade protectionism added uncertainty and major markets such as the United States and China remained sluggish.  In his first New Year address to employees, group heir apparent Euisun Chung said Hyundai Mot</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4508459</uri>
        <title>Delivery Boy Who Saved Lives Of 10 People In Mumbai Hospital Fire Gets Rs 1 Lakh As Reward</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.02745098039215677</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Home/Emergency Preparation/Safety, dmoz/Health/Public Health and Safety, dmoz/Health/Public Health and Safety/Emergency Services</categories>
        <loc_country>India</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>6</article_count>
        <total_article_count>6</total_article_count>
        <summary>The brave delivery boy who saved lives of 10 people during the fire accident at Mumbai's ESIC hospital was given a monetary award of Rs One Lakh.  Siddrameshwar Siddharam Humanabade, a food delivery boy pulled off a heroic act saving lives of numerous people at a Mumbai Hospital which was engulfed in flames on December 17, 2018. Labour minister Santosh Gangwar gave him the reward.  Also Read: Food Delivery Boy Jumps Into Mumbai Hospital That Caught Fire To Rescue Ten People  The braveheart saved </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4516577</uri>
        <title>Rajasthan's New Year Gift To Girls Is Sanitary Pad Vending Machines In All Govt Colleges</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1843137254901961</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Health/Women's Health/Menstruation</categories>
        <loc_country>India</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>6</article_count>
        <total_article_count>6</total_article_count>
        <summary>In February 2018, former Chief Minister of Rajasthan Vasundhara Raje had announced that sanitary napkins will be provided to women in rural areas.  The announcement was made as part of a new health scheme which will promote menstrual hygiene. PTI had reported that Rs 76 crore was also allotted for this initiative. As the world welcomes 2019, Rajasthan's new scheme will soon become a reality.  Sanitary napkin vending machines will be installed in all 189 government colleges, Times of India reporte</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4505520</uri>
        <title>Protesters call on Sudan president to go</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.207843137254902</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Society/Issues, dmoz/Society/Issues/Territorial Disputes, dmoz/Society/Issues/Economic</categories>
        <loc_country>Sudan</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Africa</loc_continent>
        <article_count>145</article_count>
        <total_article_count>159</total_article_count>
        <summary>Hundreds of protesters have gathered in the Sudanese city of Omdurman to call for an end to the nearly 30-year rule of President Omar al-Bashir.  The BBC's Mohamed Osman says security forces have used tear gas against some of the 300 or so demonstrators there.  Sudan has already been rocked by two weeks of sometimes deadly street demonstrations prompted by a rise in the cost of living.  The anti-government protests first erupted in mid-December over inflation.  The price of bread had tripled in s</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4506220</uri>
        <title>FG provides funds to meet ASUU demands</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.09019607843137245</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Society/Work, dmoz/Society/Issues/Labor, dmoz/Society/Work/Labor-Management Relations</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>45</article_count>
        <total_article_count>45</total_article_count>
        <summary>The protracted strike by the Academic Staff Union of Universities (ASUU) may soon to be called off.  Minister of Labour and Employment, Dr. Chris Ngige, who gave the hint in Onitsha, Anambra State said that funds had been provided to meet most of the demands of the union.  He said the Federal Government would make necessary efforts to ensure that the strike comes to an end this January.  According to Ngige, the issues that made ASUU to embark on strike were based on agreement which the union ente</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507501</uri>
        <title>Killings in Chicago fall 15% from year before</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.09019607843137245</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Science/Earth Sciences, dmoz/Science/Earth Sciences/Geophysics, dmoz/Science/Earth Sciences/Geomatics</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>6</article_count>
        <total_article_count>6</total_article_count>
        <summary>ILLINOIS Killings in Chicago fall 15% from year before  Preliminary numbers indicate that homicides in Chicago fell by about 100 last year compared with 2017, though the total again eclipsed the number of killings in Los Angeles and New York combined, according to data released Tuesday.  Police in Chicago, the nation's third-largest city, reported 561 homicides between Jan. 1 and Dec. 31, 2018. That compares with 660 homicides in 2017 and more than 770 in 2016, which marked a 19-year high that pu</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4509569</uri>
        <title>Here are the new 'Dogs of the Dow,' a simple investing strategy that beat the market last year</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.03529411764705881</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Business/Investing, dmoz/Business/Investing/Stocks and Bonds, dmoz/Business/Investing/Research and Analysis</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>17</article_count>
        <total_article_count>17</total_article_count>
        <summary>The strategy calls for the purchase of the 10 Dow members with the highest dividend yields.  The "Dogs of the Dow" beat the market in 2018. Now meet the new dogs.  One of Wall Street's classic investing strategies, perhaps the most hands-off one, kept investors relatively safe last year -- if one had bought the 10 highest-yielding stocks in the Dow Jones Industrial Average at the beginning of 2018 and held them all year long, it would have only lost 1.5 percent, versus the Dow's 6 percent annual </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4512780</uri>
        <title>Metro eliminates Saturday parking fees | WTOP</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.06666666666666665</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Business/Transportation and Logistics/Urban Transport</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>17</article_count>
        <total_article_count>17</total_article_count>
        <summary>WASHINGTON -- Starting this weekend, Metro will no longer have parking fees on Saturdays.  A $2 fee for weekend parking at Metro facilities had been implemented a year ago as part of a pilot program, but it is now being scrapped.  "Riders who use Metrorail will park for free on Saturday, with the exception of designated regional or special events," Metro said in a news release.  There could still be a charge for parking on weekends or on federal holidays if a major event is happening, such as a F</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4516681</uri>
        <title>Government shutdown causing chaos at the IRS just before tax filing season</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.04313725490196085</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Business/Accounting, dmoz/Business/Accounting/Tax Negotiation and Representation, dmoz/Home/Personal Finance/Tax Preparation</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>98</article_count>
        <total_article_count>98</total_article_count>
        <summary>Government shutdown causing chaos at the IRS just before tax filing season  Americans are used to procrastinating when it comes to their taxes. This year, tax filing season is expected to get an even bigger delay -- thanks to the government shutdown.  The Internal Revenue Service is one of the many agencies shut down since Dec. 22. Only 12 percent of its staff are working (without pay), mostly focused on security and technology. The agency is not issuing refunds, updating tax forms or answering p</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4505102</uri>
        <title>Trump: Falling gas prices are 'tax cut' for US consumers</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.0117647058823529</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Business/Energy/Oil and Gas, dmoz/Home/Consumer Information/Price Comparisons, dmoz/Shopping/Antiques and Collectibles/Advertising Collectibles</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>37</article_count>
        <total_article_count>56</total_article_count>
        <summary>RNC Spokeswoman Kayleigh McEnany on the government shutdown over the border wall funding debate.  President Trump touted steadily falling gas prices as a de facto tax cut for U.S. consumers who are paying less at the pump.  Gas prices have plunged in recent months - a decline that has occurred alongside a drop in the price of U.S. crude oil amid concerns that the marketplace is oversupplied. The average national price of gas stood at $2.25 per gallon as of Jan. 2.  "Do you think it's just luck th</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4508952</uri>
        <title>Major automakers bullish on U.S. market despite rising interest rates</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1372549019607843</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Shopping/Classifieds, dmoz/Shopping/Classifieds/Automotive, dmoz/Business/Marketing and Advertising/Salesmanship</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>285</article_count>
        <total_article_count>251</total_article_count>
        <summary>DETROIT (Reuters) - Major automakers on Thursday shrugged off declines in U.S. new vehicle sales in December and said they were bullish about 2019 even as economists warned that rising interest rates will discourage consumers from buying cars in the year ahead.  "Despite recent market turbulence, the data we have in hand suggests an economy that remains on solid footing heading into the new year," Ford Chief Economist Emily Kolinski Morris said on a conference call. "Consumers seem to be looking </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4508953</uri>
        <title>A man fired his handgun at a Taco Bell dive-thru at 1am after 'not getting enough sauce,' police say</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.1529411764705882</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Business/Human Resources/Employee Relations, dmoz/Shopping/Food/Condiments, dmoz/Home/Cooking/Sauces, Dips, Gravies, and Toppings</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>32</article_count>
        <total_article_count>32</total_article_count>
        <summary>A man fired through the window of a Taco-Bell drive-thru because he did not get enough taco sauce, police said. Oklahoma City police said he was "very upset" about "not getting enough sauce, or not getting any taco sauce" with his order. Employees locked themselves in the bathroom when the man went inside, but he left before police arrived. The police said it was "extremely fortunate" that no one was hurt.  A man fired his handgun through the window of a Taco Bell drive-thru at 1 a.m. because he </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4508992</uri>
        <title>Carnival Cruise AirShip Takes Flight; Kicks Off Month-Long Tour Of California</title>
        <event_date>2018-12-29</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.3411764705882352</sentiment>
        <categories>dmoz/Recreation/Travel, dmoz/Recreation/Travel/Specialty Travel, news/Arts and Entertainment</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>8</article_count>
        <total_article_count>12</total_article_count>
        <summary>MIAMI, Dec. 31, 2018 /PRNewswire/ -- Kicking off a year-long celebration welcoming the new Carnival Panorama to the West Coast, Carnival Cruise Line is going to extreme heights today ­- literally - as its popular Carnival AirShip makes its aerial debut in Southern California.  Inviting everyone to "Choose Fun," the 120-foot-long AirShip will fly over and visit culture and entertainment locations across the state throughout January including The Rose Parade: A Showcase of Floats on Jan. 2 as well</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4510610</uri>
        <title>Passenger stung with $252 bill for 32km Uber trip</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.01960784313725494</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Computers/Software/Device Drivers, dmoz/Computers/Programming/Drivers, dmoz/Business/Education and Training/Driving</categories>
        <loc_country>Canada</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>38</article_count>
        <total_article_count>38</total_article_count>
        <summary>Massive surcharges on Uber fares during New Year's Eve celebrations have sparked complaints from Perth revellers.  Many took to social media yesterday to protest about exorbitant charges for ride-sharing services, including one user who paid $252 for a 32km trip that took 33 minutes.  Under its surge pricing method, Uber increases fares in line with demand at busy times.  A woman who posted screen shots on social media of an Uber quote of about $200 to travel from Fremantle to Bayswater at 1.30am</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4514860</uri>
        <title>Government shutdown makes already rough farm markets even rougher</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.04313725490196074</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Business/Investing/Payment Associations, dmoz/Business/Agriculture and Forestry/Marketplaces, dmoz/Business/Agriculture and Forestry/Associations</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>9</article_count>
        <total_article_count>9</total_article_count>
        <summary>The Kinnard dairy farm milks more than 6,000 dairy cattle. Rick Wood / Milwaukee Journal Sentinel  The federal government shutdown could wreak havoc on U.S. agriculture, and the rural economy, as farmers wait on subsidy payments, loans and data they need now to make plans for the spring.  The timing could hardly be worse, according to some farmers, as they've already been hit with fallen commodity prices and the loss of foreign markets in President Donald Trump's trade wars.  Now as a result of t</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4502390</uri>
        <title>$10K to move to Vermont? Get remote worker application ready</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.192156862745098</sentiment>
        <categories>dmoz/Society/Issues/Labor, dmoz/Home/Moving and Relocating, dmoz/Home/Moving and Relocating/Moving, news/Business</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>12</article_count>
        <total_article_count>12</total_article_count>
        <summary>BURLINGTON, Vt. - Last spring, Vermont said it would offer $10,000 to remote workers who put down roots in Vermont. Do you want that money?  Then get your application ready.  The state will begin accepting applications on New Year's Day. The grants will be given out on a first-come, first-served basis, said Nate Formalarie, a spokesman for the Agency of Commerce and Community Development.  The plan, approved by Gov. Phil Scott and the Legislature last spring, sparked widespread interest - and lot</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507144</uri>
        <title>More coal plants shut down in Trump's first two years than in Obama's entire first term</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.07450980392156858</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Science/Technology/Mining, dmoz/Business/Mining and Drilling/Mineral Exploration and Extraction, dmoz/Business/Mining and Drilling/Associations</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>70</article_count>
        <total_article_count>70</total_article_count>
        <summary>The last time U.S. coal consumption was this low, Jimmy Carter was president.  Despite campaigning on a pledge to save the dirtiest of fossil fuels, President Donald Trump has presided over a faster rate of coal plant retirements in his first two years than President Barack Obama saw in his entire first term.  The U.S. Energy Information Administration (EIA) reports that while 15 gigawatts of coal-fired plants were shut down in Obama's first four years, Trump's first two years have seen some 20 g</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507610</uri>
        <title>Strive for great cause in year ahead, says Xi</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.3568627450980393</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Business/Mining and Drilling/Conferences, dmoz/Business/Chemicals/Biochemical, dmoz/Society/Issues/Global</categories>
        <loc_country>China</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>10</article_count>
        <total_article_count>10</total_article_count>
        <summary>PRESIDENT Xi Jinping has called for the whole nation to strive for "an unprecedented and great cause" in the year 2019, the 70th anniversary of the founding of the People's Republic of China.  Chinese people, who are self-reliant, hardworking and enterprising, have created a China miracle recognized by the world, he said in a New Year's Eve speech.  He vowed to rely on the people and push forward the cause step by step.  "In 2018, we had a fulfilling and focused year," Xi said, which saw the coun</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507904</uri>
        <title>The end of China's ride-sharing gig</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1215686274509804</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Recreation/Autos/Driving and Safety, dmoz/Health/Occupational Health and Safety</categories>
        <loc_country>China</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>20</article_count>
        <total_article_count>20</total_article_count>
        <summary>Over the last few years, millions of Chinese workers managed to earn extra money by being ride-hailing drivers. Many picked the gig because of its flexible schedule. For those who could not otherwise afford to own a car in China's pricy metropolises, driving around is also a status symbol, even if they are paying off car loans every month.  Most drivers on Didi Chuxing -- the startup that captured 90 percent of China's e-hailing trips in 2017 per consulting firm Bain &amp; Company -- were part-time. </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507921</uri>
        <title>OVP vows to continue helping Bicol landslide victims | Inquirer News</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.3960784313725491</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Science/Earth Sciences/Natural Disasters and Hazards, dmoz/Society/Philanthropy/Disaster Relief and Recovery</categories>
        <loc_country>Philippines</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>92</article_count>
        <total_article_count>92</total_article_count>
        <summary>The Office of the Vice President (OVP) vowed on Wednesday to continue helping the landslide victims in the Bicol region rebuild their lives.  Vice President Leni Robredo visited Sagñay, Camarines Sur on the same day to check on the search and retrieval operations and hand over financial aid and relief goods to families struck by landslides in the said town.  Robredo, a former congresswoman of the province, said it is "heartbreaking to see the damage left by Usman and to hear the stories of those</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507958</uri>
        <title>Stratospheric Shanghai property market plateaus</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business</categories>
        <loc_country>China</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>13</article_count>
        <total_article_count>13</total_article_count>
        <summary>SHANGHAI -- Shanghai's pricey real estate market appears to have peaked as condominiums glut the market and the property rent index remains flat for the last two years.  In October, developer Country Garden Holdings slashed prices on its unsold condominiums in the eastern outskirts of Shanghai from 35,000 yuan ($5,068) per sq. meter to between 26,000 yuan and 28,000 yuan. Furious owners -- many of whom never moved in -- are staging protests near their properties, demanding that the company stop m</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4508294</uri>
        <title>Get a drone for Christmas? New rules coming in for recreational users</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.05882352941176472</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Business/Transportation and Logistics, dmoz/Business/Transportation and Logistics/Aviation, dmoz/Business/Aerospace and Defense/Defense</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>95</article_count>
        <total_article_count>95</total_article_count>
        <summary>Having a drone might be a whole lot of sky-high fun, but a host of incoming new regulations are about to make their operation safer, a Civil Aviation Safety Authority (CASA) spokesman says. Reports of a rogue drone grounded planes in Gatwick Airport in England causing mass chaos in the lead-up to Christmas, and while rules already apply for Australian users things are about to get tougher. Some of the existing rules for recreational drone users include not flying higher than 120 metres above the </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4509671</uri>
        <title>Forget Uber, This Is the Real IPO Opportunity in 2019</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.08235294117647052</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Business/Investing/Stocks and Bonds, dmoz/Business/Marketing and Advertising/Consulting, dmoz/Business/Information Technology/Marketing and Advertising</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>12</article_count>
        <total_article_count>12</total_article_count>
        <summary>How many times have you read something like, "If you bought Amazon at the initial public offering, you'd have $24 gazillion today"?  (In fact, Amazon went public at $18 per share and gained well over 8,200% since then.)  And it isn't just behemoths like Amazon.com Inc. (NASDAQ: AMZN) that have rewarded IPO investors with big gains.  Square Inc. (NYSE: SQ) offered peak gains of 670% for IPO investors in just three years of trading.  Even Twitter Inc. (NYSE: TWTR) surged nearly 70% in just over a m</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4511538</uri>
        <title>China's high-speed railway length to top 30,000 km in 2019</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1607843137254903</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Business/Transportation and Logistics/Rail, dmoz/Recreation/Trains and Railroads, dmoz/Recreation/Trains and Railroads/Organizations</categories>
        <loc_country>China</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>14</article_count>
        <total_article_count>14</total_article_count>
        <summary>In this undated photo, workers from China Railway Construction Group lay tracks along the Chengdu-Guiyang high-speed railway line. (CAO NING / FOR CHINA DAILY)  BEIJING - China plans to build 3,200 km of new high-speed railways in 2019, with a total length expected to exceed 30,000 km, a top railway operator said on Wednesday.  The new high-speed railways are part of the planned development of 6,800 km of new railways for the new year as China will keep fixed-asset investment on railway on a larg</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4513949</uri>
        <title>Raffles Medical opens its first China hospital in Chongqing, - THE</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1529411764705881</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business</categories>
        <loc_country>China</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>9</article_count>
        <total_article_count>9</total_article_count>
        <summary>RAFFLES Medical Group opened a 700-bed hospital in Chongqing, making it the group's first international tertiary hospital in the country, it said in a Singapore Exchange announcement before market open on Wednesday.  The group also has medical centres providing outpatient services in seven other Chinese cities.  The Chongqing hospital, which is owned and operated by the group, has a gross floor area of 100,000 square metres and when fully opened, will offer specialist services and centres of exce</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4517822</uri>
        <title>Senate minority leader steps away to address alcoholism</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1529411764705881</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Health/Addictions, dmoz/Health/Addictions/Substance Abuse, dmoz/Society/Government/Parliaments and Legislatures</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>11</article_count>
        <total_article_count>11</total_article_count>
        <summary>ALBANY - Senate Minority Leader John Flanagan will miss the start of the new legislative session to seek additional help in his ongoing battle with alcohol dependency.  In a statement on Friday afternoon, the Long Island Republican, who led the chamber for the last three years, said the difficult decision is the right one for him and his family.  "I must now make my health and well-being my number one priority," Flanagan said. "As a result of the completion of a thorough rehabilitation and recove</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4516819</uri>
        <title>'Not sufficient': UN on Saudi trial into Jamal Khashoggi killing</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.3568627450980392</sentiment>
        <categories>dmoz/Society/Issues, news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Crime/Murder, dmoz/Society/Issues/Crime and Justice</categories>
        <loc_country>Saudi Arabia</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>61</article_count>
        <total_article_count>61</total_article_count>
        <summary>Spokeswoman Ravina Shamdasani, asked on Friday about reports that a Saudi prosecutor had sought death sentence for five suspects linked to the October 2 killing, reiterated the UN office's call for an independent investigation "with international involvement".  The UN rights office always opposed the death penalty, she added.  The comments from the UN official came a day after the high-profile trial of the 11 suspects charged with Khashoggi's murder opened in Saudi capital, Riyadh, on Thursday.  </summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4516351</uri>
        <title>Opinion | American Jews and Israeli Jews Are Headed for a Messy Breakup</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.02745098039215688</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Politics/Nationalism, dmoz/Society/Religion and Spirituality/Judaism</categories>
        <loc_country>Israel</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>51</article_count>
        <total_article_count>51</total_article_count>
        <summary>Mr. Weisman is the deputy Washington editor of The New York Times.  The events of past year brought American and Israeli Jews ever closer to a breaking point. President Trump, beloved in Israel and decidedly unloved by a majority of American Jews, moved the United States Embassy from Tel Aviv to Jerusalem in May, with the fiery evangelical pastors John Hagee and Robert Jeffress consecrating the ceremony.  In October, after the murder of 11 Jews at the Tree of Life synagogue in Pittsburgh, Preside</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4516041</uri>
        <title>Egypt's President El-Sisi denies holding political prisoners</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.1215686274509804</sentiment>
        <categories>dmoz/Society/Issues, news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Politics, dmoz/Society/Issues/Warfare and Conflict</categories>
        <loc_country>Egypt</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Africa</loc_continent>
        <article_count>43</article_count>
        <total_article_count>43</total_article_count>
        <summary>Egyptian President Abdel Fattah el-Sisi sat down with Scott Pelley to make news on 60 Minutes and did when he confirmed his military was working with Israel against terrorists in North Sinai. But other questions, including jailing his opponents to maintain his regime and the massacre of 800 civilians by Egypt when he was Defense Minister were not the kind of news his government wanted broadcast. The 60 Minutes team was contacted by the Egyptian Ambassador shortly after and told the interview coul</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4515886</uri>
        <title>Fratricide in Full Bloom as Israeli Election Campaign Heats Up</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1529411764705881</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Recreation/Parties/Planning, dmoz/Home/Entertaining/Party Planning, dmoz/Shopping/Entertainment/Party Supplies</categories>
        <loc_country>Israel</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>20</article_count>
        <total_article_count>20</total_article_count>
        <summary>JERUSALEM -- With elections a few months away, it is political fratricide season in Israel: From left to right, candidates are sticking knives in the ribs of their natural allies in hopes of elevating their own chances of succeeding Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu.  This week, the Zionist Union, a four-year-old liberal alliance, blew itself up as the Labor Party chief, Avi Gabbay, humiliated the veteran politician Tzipi Livni by abruptly breaking with her and her boutique party Hatnuah (The Mov</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4514473</uri>
        <title>Opinion | China's Gulag for Muslims </title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.1294117647058823</sentiment>
        <categories>dmoz/Society/Issues, news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Religion and Spirituality/Islam</categories>
        <loc_country>China</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>16</article_count>
        <total_article_count>16</total_article_count>
        <summary>In modern-day "re-education" prisons, Beijing is forcing ethnic Uighurs to forsake their religion. Why don't Muslim governments rise up in anger?  One of the darkest episodes of the 20th century was the gulag -- the Soviet system of forced labor camps where dissidents were imprisoned in terrible conditions, often to perish. The camps were established by Lenin, expanded by Stalin and finally exposed to the world by the great Russian author Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn, with his 1973 masterpiece, "The Gu</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4514192</uri>
        <title>Controversy surrounding Trump's Bedminster club grows more serious</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.07450980392156858</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Work, dmoz/Society/Issues/Immigration, dmoz/Sports/Golf</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>13</article_count>
        <total_article_count>13</total_article_count>
        <summary>About a month ago, the New York Times published a striking portrait of a Guatemalan immigrant named Victorina Morales, who entered the United States illegally many years ago, and in 2013, began working at the Trump National Golf Club in Bedminster, N.J. As a presidential candidate, Donald Trump assured voters he hadn't hired "illegal immigrants." Morales wanted the world to know that wasn't true.  At first, this looked like a story about a brave woman, coming forward despite the risks to her pers</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4511722</uri>
        <title>'What Will I Not Miss?' In California, a Long Farewell From Jerry Brown</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1058823529411765</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>35</article_count>
        <total_article_count>35</total_article_count>
        <summary>WILLIAMS, Calif. -- It's time to add another name to the farewell tour circuit in this year of Elton John, Joan Baez, Paul Simon and Ozzy Osbourne: Edmund G. Brown Jr., the governor of California.  There was the invitation-only reception for 2,000 guests at a Sacramento basketball arena; the appearance on "Meet the Press" this past Sunday to talk about President Trump and offer dark warnings about global warming; and the interviews with The Los Angeles Times, The Sacramento Bee and many others. O</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4511370</uri>
        <title>NYC traffic injuries are up despite drop in fatalities</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.1215686274509804</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Issues/Transportation, dmoz/Recreation/Roads and Highways/Online Traffic Cameras, dmoz/Society/Death/Near Death Experiences</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>6</article_count>
        <total_article_count>6</total_article_count>
        <summary>Traffic deaths may be down under Mayor de Blasio's Vision Zero program, but there are more crashes since the program began and a steadily rising injury toll, ­according to NYPD data.  Collisions on city streets increased more than 11 percent between 2014 and 2018, statistics show. In 2014, there were 205,486, and that number rose to 228,227 in 2018.  During that same time, collisions resulting in injuries increased by 18 percent, from 37,556 in 2014 to 44,508 in 2018.  Overall injuries are also </summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4511244</uri>
        <title>For Bernie Sanders, Claims of Sexism in 2016 Campaign Hang Over 2020 Bid</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.08235294117647063</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Issues/Violence and Abuse, dmoz/Society/Politics/Campaigns and Elections, dmoz/Society/Sexuality</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>109</article_count>
        <total_article_count>109</total_article_count>
        <summary>In February 2016, Giulianna Di Lauro, a Latino outreach strategist for Senator Bernie Sanders's presidential operation, complained to her supervisor that she had been harassed by a campaign surrogate whom she drove to events ahead of the Democratic primary in Nevada.  She said the surrogate told her she had "beautiful curly hair" and asked if he could touch it, Ms. Di Lauro said in an interview. Thinking he would just touch a strand, she consented. But she said that he ran his hand through her ha</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4505121</uri>
        <title>Netflix criticized for yanking comedian's episode in Saudi</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.2784313725490196</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Society/Issues, news/Politics, dmoz/Arts/Television/Programs, dmoz/Home/Consumer Information/Arts and Entertainment</categories>
        <loc_country>Turkey</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>605</article_count>
        <total_article_count>541</total_article_count>
        <summary>Human rights group Amnesty International said Saudi Arabia's censorship of Netflix is "further proof of a relentless crackdown on freedom of expression." Netflix said it was simply complying with a local law.  Netflix faced criticism Wednesday from human rights groups for pulling an episode in Saudi Arabia of comedian Hasan Minhaj's "Patriot Act" series that criticized the kingdom's powerful crown prince.  The American comedian used his second episode, released Oct. 28, to criticize Crown Prince </summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4502815</uri>
        <title>Bulandshahr: Inspector Subodh Kumar Singh became 'hopeless' and shot himself, claims BJP MLA</title>
        <event_date>2018-12-29</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.3490196078431372</sentiment>
        <categories>dmoz/Society/Law/Law Enforcement, dmoz/Society/Issues/Violence and Abuse, news/Politics</categories>
        <loc_country>India</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>29</article_count>
        <total_article_count>54</total_article_count>
        <summary>Devendra Singh Lodhi also claimed that the policeman was not specifically targeted in the violence.  A Bharatiya Janata Party MLA from Uttar Pradesh on Friday claimed that Inspector Subodh Kumar Singh, who was among two people killed in Bulandshahr district earlier this month, shot himself after he became "hopeless", ANI reported.  "While trying to save himself, the cop became hopeless and fired at himself in haste," said Devendra Singh Lodhi. "He was not targeted by anyone; it was a mob that got</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4505965</uri>
        <title>India, Pakistan Exchange Lists Of Prisoners</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.003921568627450966</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Crime/Prisons, dmoz/Society/Issues/Crime and Justice, dmoz/Computers/Artificial Life/Iterated Prisoner Dilemma</categories>
        <loc_country>Pakistan</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>53</article_count>
        <total_article_count>53</total_article_count>
        <summary>NEW DELHI -- India and Pakistan Tuesday exchanged details of civilian prisoners and fishermen lodged in each other's jails.The Ministry of External Affairs or MEA said India handed over to Pakistan lists of 249 Pakistani civilian prisoners and 98 fishermen in its custody.Pakistan has shared lists of 54 civilian prisoners and 483 fishermen in its custody, who are Indians or are believed-to-be-Indians.The lists were exchanged in keeping with the provisions of a 2008 agreement under which such lists</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4504970</uri>
        <title>Why Is Trump Spouting Russian Propaganda?</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.02745098039215688</sentiment>
        <categories>dmoz/Society/Issues, news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Issues/Peace, dmoz/Society/Issues/Warfare and Conflict</categories>
        <loc_country>Afghanistan</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>375</article_count>
        <total_article_count>381</total_article_count>
        <summary>The president's endorsement of the U.S.S.R.'s invasion of Afghanistan echoes a narrative promoted by Vladimir Putin.  It was only one moment in a 90-minute stream of madness.  President Donald Trump convened a Cabinet meeting, at which he invited all its members to praise him for his stance on the border wall and the government shutdown. There's always a lively competition to see which member of the Cabinet can grovel most abjectly. The newcomer Matthew Whitaker may be only the acting attorney ge</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4506449</uri>
        <title>Desperate migrants are found hiding in MATTRESSES</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.05882352941176472</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Shopping/Home and Garden/Walls, dmoz/Society/Issues/Labor</categories>
        <loc_country>Spain</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Europe</loc_continent>
        <article_count>15</article_count>
        <total_article_count>15</total_article_count>
        <summary>Footage shows guards cutting through plastic and fabric to reveal men inside  This is the extraordinary moment two migrants emerged from inside mattresses during their bid to reach Europe from Africa.  The sub-Saharan men were arrested after border guards found them at a check-point between Melilla, a Spanish enclave on the north African coast, and Morocco.  It is understood to be the first time the method has been used to smuggle migrants and there are fears criminal gangs could increasingly use</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507173</uri>
        <title>Slain Archana's daughter tearfully recalls last hug</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.192156862745098</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Law/Law Enforcement</categories>
        <loc_country>India</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>90</article_count>
        <total_article_count>90</total_article_count>
        <summary>New Delhi: Not a single person in the family had thought that it would be their last hug until the shots were fired. The joy of New Year turned into grief for the Gupta family as the 42-year-old architect, who sustained head injuries from a bullet fired by a family friend, succumbed to her injuries on Wednesday.  Victim Archana's daughter, Hoshika Gupta, hadn't imagined even in her wildest dreams that the hug her mother gave her would be the last one as minutes after the hug she was shot by a fam</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507803</uri>
        <title>Aligarh: 60 stray cattle die in a week due to 'cold and weakness', say police</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.04313725490196085</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Issues/Animal Welfare, dmoz/Recreation/Humor/Animals</categories>
        <loc_country>India</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>39</article_count>
        <total_article_count>48</total_article_count>
        <summary>After coming to know about the deaths, a team of district administration, including veterinary doctors and police, rushed to the spot to inquire into the incident on Monday.  In the last one week, as many as 60 stray cattle, including cows and calves, kept in a makeshift shed died of "cold and weakness" in Tappal area of Aligarh district, police said.  Police had transported 1,800 cattle in the last one week to a cow shelter run by one Shiv Dutt Sharma at Jarkari town, but the latter shifted most</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4514842</uri>
        <title>City of Keene in Dispute with Local Restaurant Owner Over 'Pho Keene Great' Name</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.09019607843137245</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Business/Business Services/Signage, dmoz/Recreation/Roads and Highways/Signs and Signals, dmoz/Recreation/Food/Dining Guides</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>11</article_count>
        <total_article_count>11</total_article_count>
        <summary>The City of Keene is asking a Vietnamese restaurant slated to open this spring to change its name.  The restaurant has a lease with the city to operate out of the same building as City Hall.  But its proposed name, Pho Keene Great, has prompted complaints, said City Manager Elizabeth Dragon.  Pho, pronounced "fuh," is a kind of Vietnamese soup. "Pho Keene" is intended to sound like a profanity, Dragon said.  Under the terms of the lease, the restaurant must get permission from the city before han</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4515847</uri>
        <title>Analysis | Britain clings to imperial nostalgia as Brexit looms</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1607843137254903</sentiment>
        <categories>dmoz/Society/Issues, dmoz/Society/Government, news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Issues/Economic</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>16</article_count>
        <total_article_count>16</total_article_count>
        <summary>By Ishaan Tharoor Ishaan Tharoor Reporter covering foreign affairs, geopolitics and history January 4 at 12:59 AM  Want smart analysis of the most important news in your inbox every weekday along with other global reads, interesting ideas and opinions to know? Sign up for the Today's WorldView newsletter.  (Adrian Dennis)  British Prime Minister Theresa May may be on her last legs. Last month, she delayed a parliamentary vote on her much-maligned Brexit deal with Brussels, fearing it would go dow</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4514589</uri>
        <title>New sheriffs in town as African Americans win top law enforcement posts in N.C.</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.09019607843137256</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Issues/Immigration, dmoz/Recreation/Climbing/Ice Climbing, dmoz/Games/Party Games/Icebreaker Games</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>9</article_count>
        <total_article_count>9</total_article_count>
        <summary>By Barry Yeoman January 4 at 7:00 AM  DURHAM, N. C. -- Three days after he was sworn in as Durham County's new sheriff last month, Clarence Birkhead ended his department's cooperative relationship with U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement. Within a week, Birkhead's staff rebuffed ICE 11 times, releasing immigrants from the county jail rather than holding them for the federal agency to pick up as a first step toward deportation.  Other new sheriffs were doing much the same. In Mecklenburg and </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4513777</uri>
        <title>'Electronic Wall' E-Verify Suspended As Border Security Shutdown Fight Persists</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.05882352941176472</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Issues/Immigration, dmoz/Society/Transgendered/Law, dmoz/Society/Genealogy/Emigration and Immigration</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>25</article_count>
        <total_article_count>25</total_article_count>
        <summary>The government shutdown began with the president's demand for border security money. But it's also shut down E-Verify, a federal program that's supposed to prevent immigrants from working illegally.  If U.S. employers want to check whether their prospective hires are eligible to work, they can't. The E-Verify database is "currently unavailable due to a lapse in government appropriations," according to a note on the government-run web site.  "There's an irony there," says Julie Pace, an attorney s</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4512676</uri>
        <title>Opinion | Kamala Harris's Dark Knights</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.03529411764705892</sentiment>
        <categories>dmoz/Society, news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Politics, dmoz/Society/Relationships/Marriage</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>5</article_count>
        <total_article_count>5</total_article_count>
        <summary>By The Editorial Board The Editorial Board The Wall Street Journal BiographyThe Editorial Board @WSJopinion WSJOpinion Jan. 2, 2019 6:57 p.m. ET  We're still a year from the 2020 presidential primaries, but Senator Kamala Harris is already showing America how far the Democratic Party has strayed from its roots.  Democrats rightly take pride in the 1928 nomination of Gov. Al Smith, which signaled the party's affirmation that Catholics had a place in American public life. Ditto for Jack Kennedy, wh</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4512539</uri>
        <title>Turkey seeks nearly 150 arrests over Gulen ties: report - Global Village Space</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.2470588235294118</sentiment>
        <categories>dmoz/Society/Issues, news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Issues/Warfare and Conflict, dmoz/Society/Issues/Terrorism</categories>
        <loc_country>Turkey</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>20</article_count>
        <total_article_count>20</total_article_count>
        <summary>Turkish police on Friday launched nationwide raids to detain nearly 150 people, including military personnel, suspected of ties to the group blamed for the 2016 attempted coup, local media reported.  Prosecutors in Istanbul, Konya and Ankara issued arrest warrants for 137 people as part of different investigations into followers of US-based Muslim preacher Fethullah Gulen, state news agency Anadolu and NTV broadcaster reported.  Tens of thousands of people have been arrested over alleged links to</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4511089</uri>
        <title>Opinion | Republicans should be alarmed by this sign of intelligent life in the Democratic Party</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Politics, dmoz/Society/Politics/Campaigns and Elections, dmoz/Society/Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual/Politics</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>5</article_count>
        <total_article_count>5</total_article_count>
        <summary>By George F. Will George F. Will Columnist covering politics and domestic and foreign affairs Columnist January 2 at 6:04 PM  If Republicans have a lick of sense, they are alarmed by a recent sign of intelligent life in the other party. The sign is the election by Democrats in the House of Representatives of Rep. Cheri Bustos (Ill.) as chair of the Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee. In November, she won a fourth term by 24 percentage points -- the largest margin of any Democrat running </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4511026</uri>
        <title>Kansas Sen. Pat Roberts announces he won't seek reelection in 2020</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1058823529411765</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Politics/Campaigns and Elections, dmoz/Society/Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual/Politics, dmoz/Society/Government/Parliaments and Legislatures</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>56</article_count>
        <total_article_count>59</total_article_count>
        <summary>By Dave Weigel and Sean Sullivan Sean Sullivan Reporter covering national politics January 4 at 12:35 PM  Sen. Pat Roberts, the blunt-speaking Kansan who worked closely with Democrats on helping the nation's farmers and protecting food stamps for millions of low-income Americans, announced Friday that he would not seek reelection in 2020.  Roberts, 82, who had conferred with his family over the holidays, said at a news conference in Manhattan, Kan., "I am announcing that I will serve the remainde</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4510195</uri>
        <title>Texas County Swears In 17 Black Female Judges In 'Extraordinary Moment In History'</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1137254901960785</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Politics/Campaigns and Elections</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>27</article_count>
        <total_article_count>27</total_article_count>
        <summary>New representation and Black Girl Magic came to a Texas county this week when 17 black women were sworn in as new judges.  The newly-elected officials made headlines in November when they won their races for various courts in Harris County, which includes Houston and surrounding areas. They were sworn in on Tuesday.  "January 1, 2019 at noon will be an extraordinary moment in history for all of us in Harris County, Houston, Texas," Judge LaShawn Williams wrote on Facebook last month ahead of the </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4517828</uri>
        <title>What It Looks Like To Have A Record Number Of Women In The House Of Representatives</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1058823529411765</sentiment>
        <categories>dmoz/Sports/Women, news/Politics, dmoz/Health/Women's Health/Smoking, dmoz/Health/Women's Health/Organizations</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>19</article_count>
        <total_article_count>19</total_article_count>
        <summary>One hundred twenty-seven. That's how many women will be in Congress this year, up from 110 in the previous Congress.  It's a jump that's simultaneously so big and so small.  On the one hand, there are 15 percent more women in this Congress than there were last session. There are now a record number of women of color in the House. There are also a slew of firsts: Congress will get its first Native American women, Muslim women, and youngest woman member ever.  On the other hand, this year's record-</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4505657</uri>
        <title>House passes bill to end US government shutdown without border wall money</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.05882352941176472</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Issues/Housing, dmoz/Business/Real Estate/Residential, dmoz/Shopping/Home and Garden/Walls</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>2798</article_count>
        <total_article_count>2331</total_article_count>
        <summary>Fog surrounds the U.S. Capitol building on November 6, 2018 in Washington, DC. Today millions of Americans will head to the polls and vote in the midterm elections that will decide what party will control the House of Representatives and the U.S. Senate.  The new Democratic-held House passed legislation Thursday night that would end a partial government shutdown.  Passage of the spending packages will not move Congress closer to reopening nine unfunded federal departments for now. As the measures</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4515340</uri>
        <title>Lots of People in Delaware Seem Cool With This Racist Parade</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.09019607843137256</sentiment>
        <categories>dmoz/Society/Issues, news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual/Pride Celebrations</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>11</article_count>
        <total_article_count>11</total_article_count>
        <summary>There's nothing funny about Border Patrol agents pepper spraying immigrants, or children being separated from their families. The deaths of two children in the custody of U.S. immigration authorities is nothing to laugh at.  And yet the "Hummers Parade," an annual event in Middletown, DE, decided it was cool to mock all of these things. The parade, a spoof of Philadelphia's annual Mummers Parade, has apparently been running for 48 years.  The parade "has no registration, membership, or rules. It'</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4510054</uri>
        <title>New House rules to allow Democrats to defend Obamacare</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.192156862745098</sentiment>
        <categories>dmoz/Society/Law, news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Transgendered/Law, dmoz/Society/Law/Legal Information</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>42</article_count>
        <total_article_count>42</total_article_count>
        <summary>Chat with us in Facebook Messenger. Find out what's happening in the world as it unfolds.  (CNN)House Democrats are moving quickly to defend the Affordable Care Act once they retake control of the chamber Thursday.  As part of its rules package for the 116th Congress, the party is granting itself authorization to intervene in the lawsuit that threatens to bring down the landmark health reform law. It directs the House's Office of General Counsel to represent lawmakers in any litigation involving </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4509653</uri>
        <title>Ocasio-Cortez Rips Dem Leadership for Treating Planet-Saving Green New Deal as 'Controversial'</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.05098039215686279</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Science/Environment/Climate Change, dmoz/Society/Issues/Environment, dmoz/Science/Earth Sciences/Paleogeography and Paleoclimatology</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>73</article_count>
        <total_article_count>73</total_article_count>
        <summary>Incoming Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez took aim at the Democratic Party on Monday over the newly-announced climate crisis committee -- a body she and other progressives say lacks the teeth needed to avert planetary disaster.  In a Twitter thread, Ocasio-Cortez said that her proposal for a select committee on a Green New Deal -- a key demand of the youth-led Sunrise Movement -- contained "3 simple elements: 1. No fossil fuel money on climate cmte 2. Offer solutions for impacted communities 3. Draf</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4509595</uri>
        <title>Oregon man tries stealing bike in front of police station, immediately gets arrested</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.2627450980392156</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Sports/Cycling/Bike Shops, dmoz/Shopping/Sports/Cycling, dmoz/Society/Law/Law Enforcement</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>19</article_count>
        <total_article_count>19</total_article_count>
        <summary>WATCH Man arrested after attempting to steal bike from in front of police station  It's almost like he planned to get caught.  An Oregon man was arrested last week for trying to steal a bike that was locked up at the front door of a police station in Gladstone, about 10 miles south of Portland.  The Gladstone Police Department caught it on surveillance video. The footage shows suspect Adam Valle, 26, wearing a mask as he cuts the lock off the bike with a bolt cutter, just before Sgt. Matt Okerman</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4508388</uri>
        <title>Melania Trump posts festive New Year's selfie after Mar-a-Lago bash</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.3254901960784313</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Government/Government-Related Organizations</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>5</article_count>
        <total_article_count>9</total_article_count>
        <summary>Coverage of First Lady Melania Trump has been subjected to harsh treatment at the hands of everyone from late-night comedians to mainstream news organizations. From mocking her accent, to slamming her choices of Christmas décor, Melania is constantly mocked and attacked by prominent liberals and media members. Here are some of the most over-the-top attacks on the first lady of 2018.  Melania Trump took a festive New Year's selfie and posted it to her Twitter account, and the media has yet to tak</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4505605</uri>
        <title>Manchester Victoria station stabbings treated as terror attack</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.3647058823529412</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Issues/Warfare and Conflict, dmoz/Society/Law/Law Enforcement, dmoz/Society/Issues/Terrorism</categories>
        <loc_country>United Kingdom</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Europe</loc_continent>
        <article_count>317</article_count>
        <total_article_count>347</total_article_count>
        <summary>A 25-year-old man was arrested on suspicion of attempted murder after the incident, which happened shortly before 9pm.  Two knives were recovered at the scene and a property is being searched in the Cheetham Hill area.  In a briefing on Tuesday morning, police said they were keeping an open mind about the motive.  They have not yet confirmed whether the suspect is a British national.  The three victims were taken to a nearby hospital in a "serious" condition but their injuries are not thought to </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4505406</uri>
        <title>Kim and Trump Back at Square One: If U.S. Keeps Sanctions, North Will Keep Nuclear Program</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.08235294117647052</sentiment>
        <categories>dmoz/Society/Issues, news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Issues/Warfare and Conflict, dmoz/Sports/Martial Arts/Korean</categories>
        <loc_country>North Korea</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>639</article_count>
        <total_article_count>649</total_article_count>
        <summary>Nearly two years into his presidency and more than six months after his historic summit meeting with Kim Jong-un of North Korea, President Trump finds himself essentially back where he was at the beginning in achieving the ambitious goal of getting Mr. Kim to relinquish his nuclear arsenal.  That was the essential message of Mr. Kim's annual New Year's televised speech, where he reiterated that international sanctions must be lifted before North Korea will give up a single weapon, dismantle a sin</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4505427</uri>
        <title>Trump: Iran 'can do what they want' in Syria</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.02745098039215688</sentiment>
        <categories>dmoz/Society/Issues, news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Issues/Warfare and Conflict</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>209</article_count>
        <total_article_count>244</total_article_count>
        <summary>WASHINGTON -- US President Donald Trump on Wednesday gave Iran free rein to further entrench itself in Syria, acknowledging Tehran's attempts to bolster its presence in the beleaguered country.  "They can do what they want there, frankly," he told reporters, referring to Iranian forces.  Trump's comments came two weeks after he rattled Jerusalem by announcing that he would pull all American troops out of Syria. US soldiers had been leading the coalition against the Islamic State terror group, whi</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4504743</uri>
        <title>Taiwan won't give ground on sovereignty, Tsai Ing-wen says in new year address</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2</sentiment>
        <categories>dmoz/Society/Issues/Territorial Disputes, news/Politics, dmoz/Business/Mining and Drilling/Conferences, dmoz/Business/Chemicals/Biochemical</categories>
        <loc_country>Taiwan</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>31</article_count>
        <total_article_count>46</total_article_count>
        <summary>Taipei will not give any ground on sovereignty despite the ruling Democratic Progressive Party's landslide defeat in local government elections late last year, the island's leader said ahead of a major speech on Taiwan by Chinese President Xi Jinping.  In late November, the opposition Kuomintang won control of 15 of 22 cities and counties - including the former DPP stronghold of Kaohsiung, a result some politicians said reflected public support for the KMT's more Beijing-friendly policies.  But T</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4505784</uri>
        <title>Cooperation best for both China and U.S., Xi tells Trump</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.3960784313725489</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Issues/Economic, dmoz/Business/Mining and Drilling/Conferences, dmoz/Business/Chemicals/Biochemical</categories>
        <loc_country>China</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>26</article_count>
        <total_article_count>30</total_article_count>
        <summary>BEIJING (Reuters) - History shows that cooperation is the best choice for both China and the United States, Chinese President Xi Jinping told U.S. President Donald Trump in a congratulatory message on Tuesday to mark 40 years since the establishment of diplomatic relations.  The two countries agreed last month to a 90-day temporary ceasefire in their bitter trade war to give them time to hold fresh talks to try and end a dispute that has seen them level increasingly severe tariffs on each others'</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4504672</uri>
        <title>Baby saved after 35 hours in subzero conditions following Russia blast</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.2392156862745098</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Politics, dmoz/Business/Construction and Maintenance/Building Types, dmoz/Business/Chemicals/Explosives, dmoz/Computers/Software/Build Management</categories>
        <loc_country>Russia</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Europe</loc_continent>
        <article_count>407</article_count>
        <total_article_count>550</total_article_count>
        <summary>A 10-month old boy was rescued alive after spending more than 35 hours in subzero conditions buried under the rubble of a collapsed building in Russia.  Emergency crews temporarily suspended their search for survivors Tuesday amid fears that remnants of the 10-story apartment block were too unstable following the deadly New Year's Eve gas explosion.  But a short time later rescuers heard a child crying and rushed to save it, regional Gov. Boris Dubrovsky said on his official Telegram account. Dub</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4506156</uri>
        <title>As Hong Kong tightens screws on rebellion, democracy moves further out of reach</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.06666666666666665</sentiment>
        <categories>dmoz/Society/Issues/Territorial Disputes, news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Politics, dmoz/Society/Politics/Democracy</categories>
        <loc_country>China</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>38</article_count>
        <total_article_count>38</total_article_count>
        <summary>Chat with us in Facebook Messenger. Find out what's happening in the world as it unfolds.  Hong Kong (CNN)"If this is the cup I must take, I will drink with no regret."  Benny Tai was defiant and emotional as he faced the court. Outside, he and his fellow defendants raised their fists and supporters displayed yellow umbrellas, the symbol of Hong Kong's beleaguered pro-democracy movement. That movement is looking shakier than ever, as Tai and others begin the new year facing possible jail time -- </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>spa-1427574</uri>
        <title>Brazil's new far-right President removes protections for Indigenous people</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.09019607843137245</sentiment>
        <categories>dmoz/Society/Issues, news/Politics, dmoz/Society/Politics, dmoz/Society/Issues/Economic</categories>
        <loc_country>Brazil</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>South America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>1457</article_count>
        <total_article_count>362</total_article_count>
        <summary>Brazil's new far-right President Jair Bolsonaro has stripped the government department charged with protecting the country's Indigenous people of much of its responsibilities, which distressed critics say could lead to the destruction of dozens of tribes.  Brazilian newspaper Folha de S.Paulo reported the decision was announced just hours after the new President was sworn in as the country's leader on Tuesday (local time), and confirmed a pre-election pledge to roll back Indigenous rights and pro</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4506250</uri>
        <title>AI predictions for 2019 from Yann LeCun, Hilary Mason, Andrew Ng, and Rumman Chowdhury</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2313725490196079</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Technology, dmoz/Computers/Artificial Intelligence/Games, dmoz/Computers/Artificial Intelligence/Philosophy, dmoz/Computers/Artificial Intelligence/Publications</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>53</article_count>
        <total_article_count>53</total_article_count>
        <summary>Above: Left to right: Cloudera machine learning general manager Hilary Mason, Accenture global responsible AI lead Rumman Chowdhury, Facebook AI Research director Yann LeCun, and Google Brain cofounder Andrew Ng  Artificial intelligence is cast all at once as the technology that will save the world and end it.  To cut through the noise and hype, VentureBeat spoke with luminaries whose views on the right way to do AI have been informed by years of working with some of the biggest tech and industry</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4510590</uri>
        <title>Big Tech May Look Troubled, but It's Just Getting Started</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.01960784313725483</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Technology, dmoz/Computers/Internet/Searching, dmoz/Society/Issues/Business, dmoz/Business/Information Technology/Marketing and Advertising</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>7</article_count>
        <total_article_count>7</total_article_count>
        <summary>SAN JOSE, Calif. -- Silicon Valley ended 2018 somewhere it had never been: embattled.  Lawmakers across the political spectrum say Big Tech, for so long the exalted embodiment of American genius, has too much power. Once seen as a force for making our lives better and our brains smarter, tech is now accused of inflaming, radicalizing, dumbing down and squeezing the masses. Tech company stocks have been pummeled from their highs. Regulation looms. Even tech executives are calling for it.  In the f</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4511411</uri>
        <title>Ocean Cleanup device in Great Pacific Garbage Patch breaks</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.04313725490196085</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Technology, dmoz/Recreation/Collecting/Patches, dmoz/Science/Earth Sciences/Oceanography, dmoz/Business/Chemicals/Polymers</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>28</article_count>
        <total_article_count>28</total_article_count>
        <summary>SAN FRANCISCO -- A 60-foot chunk of the Ocean Cleanup device, deployed with much fanfare in the Great Pacific Garbage Patch in October, has broken off and the entire plastic collection system will now be towed back to port for an overhaul and upgrade.  The break was discovered on Dec. 29 during a routine inspection by the cleanup system's crew. A 60-foot end section of the 2,000-foot boom that corrals the plastic had detached, Boyan Slat, the Cleanup's CEO, posted on the Dutch non-profit's blog o</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4515761</uri>
        <title>Huawei demotes two employees and cuts their pay after tweeting from iPhone</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.04313725490196085</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Technology, dmoz/Business/Human Resources/Employee Relations, dmoz/Computers/Systems/Handhelds, dmoz/Computers/Security/Virtual Private Networks</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>156</article_count>
        <total_article_count>156</total_article_count>
        <summary>Huawei has demoted and cut the pay of two of its employees after an iPhone was used to send a New Year's greeting from the company's official Twitter account. In a memo seen by both Reuters and Bloomberg, the company's corporate senior vice president Chen Lifang said that the incident had "caused damage to the Huawei brand." In addition to the demotion and a 5,000 yuan (around $728) monthly pay cut, the January 3rd memo said that one of the employees would also see their pay rank frozen for 12 mo</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507395</uri>
        <title>Hacker Group Releases '9/11 Papers', Claims Leaks Will 'Burn Down' the US Deep State</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.2549019607843137</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Technology, dmoz/Society/Law/Legal Information, dmoz/Society/Issues/Terrorism, dmoz/Computers/Hacking</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>47</article_count>
        <total_article_count>47</total_article_count>
        <summary>The document dump is just a fraction of the 18,000 secret documents related to the September 11, 2001 terrorist attacks believed to have been stolen from insurers, law firms, and government agencies.  The Dark Overlord initially threatened to release the 10GB of data unless the hacked firms paid an unspecified bitcoin ransom. However, on Wednesday, the group announced a "tiered compensation plan" in which the public could make bitcoin payments to unlock the troves of documents.  A day later, the </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507905</uri>
        <title>Google wins US approval for new radar-based motion sensor</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2862745098039217</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Technology, dmoz/Computers/Internet/Searching, dmoz/Business/Electronics and Electrical/Instrumentation</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>81</article_count>
        <total_article_count>81</total_article_count>
        <summary>Alphabet Inc's Google unit won approval from US regulators to deploy a radar-based motion sensing device known as Project Soli.  The Federal Communications Commission (FCC) said in an order late on Monday that it would grant Google a waiver to operate the Soli sensors at higher power levels than currently allowed. The FCC said the sensors can also be operated aboard aircraft.  The FCC said the decision "will serve the public interest by providing for innovative device control features using touch</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4505527</uri>
        <title>Artificial Intelligence could be first 'resident' on Mars, hints Musk</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.003921568627450966</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Technology</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>16</article_count>
        <total_article_count>21</total_article_count>
        <summary>Responding to a tweet that asked Musk what his thoughts were on the first Martian being an intelligent machine rather than a human, he replied: "30%."  Tech billionaire and SpaceX CEO Elon Musk wants to establish a base on Mars, and he has indicated the first resident on the planet could be Artificial Intelligence (AI).  Responding to a tweet that asked Musk what his thoughts were on the first Martian being an intelligent machine rather than a human, he replied: "30%."  How Musk came up with this</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4510331</uri>
        <title>'Workaround systems' help print US newspapers hit by cyber attack: source</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.1529411764705882</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Technology, dmoz/Business/Publishing and Printing, dmoz/Society/Issues/Warfare and Conflict, dmoz/Society/Issues/Terrorism</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>12</article_count>
        <total_article_count>12</total_article_count>
        <summary>It is the latest in a string of cyber attacks that have disrupted operations at manufacturing plants, hospitals, 911 emergency dispatch centers and companies around the world.  Tribune Publishing Co used "workaround systems" to help print major US newspapers including the Los Angeles Times on Sunday and Monday as the company recovers from a cyber attack, a source familiar with the operation said.  The company has made "lots of progress" in repairing infected computer systems, the person said. Sti</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4510500</uri>
        <title>Ajit Pai thanks Congress for helping him kill net neutrality rules</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.08235294117647052</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Technology, dmoz/Society/Law/Legal Information, dmoz/Computers/Internet/Publications, dmoz/Computers/Internet/Policy</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>28</article_count>
        <total_article_count>28</total_article_count>
        <summary>Democratic effort to reverse repeal fell short as Congressional session ended.  Ajit Pai today celebrated a victory in his ongoing quest to prevent the US government from enforcing net neutrality rules.  The Pai-led Federal Communications Commission repealed Obama-era net neutrality rules, but the repeal could have been reversed by Congress if it acted before the end of its session. Democrats won a vote to reverse the repeal in the Senate but weren't able to get enough votes in the House of Repre</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4510937</uri>
        <title>Earthquake early warning app for LA County available for download</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.0117647058823529</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Technology, dmoz/Science/Earth Sciences, dmoz/Science/Earth Sciences/Geophysics, dmoz/Shopping/Antiques and Collectibles/Religious and Inspirational</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>50</article_count>
        <total_article_count>50</total_article_count>
        <summary>Mayor Eric Garcetti tweeted this image of the ShakeAlertLA app. (mayorofla/Twitter)  When the big one comes, even seconds of warning prior to shaking could save your life. And if you live in Los Angeles County, the ShakeAlertLA app could do just that.  The app is now available for download for Apple and Android phones. Those who download the app would receive a push alert, possibly up to 20 seconds before an earthquake hits L.A. County.  MORE: USGS, Caltech officials announce rollout of West Coas</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4508358</uri>
        <title>Huawei Mate 20 Pro vs Google Pixel 3 XL review | TheINQUIRER </title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1529411764705881</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Technology, dmoz/Computers/Internet/Searching</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>47</article_count>
        <total_article_count>47</total_article_count>
        <summary>THESE DAYS, phone users want their devices to boast epic cameras, and the Huawei Mate 20 Pro and Google Pixel 3 XL are by far the most impressive the market has to offer right now.  But which handset has the edge? And what about battery life, screen, design and performance? If we were to compare all the features that make a great smartphone between these two handsets, which one would win?  Well, that's exactly what we're about to find out. We've pitted the Mate 20 Pro and Pixel 3 XL in a battle o</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4516352</uri>
        <title>Amazon Alexa a "DEMON device" that gathers information that can be used to blackmail you for life</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2392156862745098</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Technology</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>30</article_count>
        <total_article_count>30</total_article_count>
        <summary>(Natural News) Millions of unwitting "sheeple" have willingly outfitted their homes and offices with so-called "smart" speakers like Amazon's Alexa device, which is marketed as a convenience assistant for getting things done simply using only your voice. But as revealed by Justus Knight in a recent video update to his YouTube channel, Alexa is, practically speaking, an always-listening demon device that can monitor, track, and record people's conversations for blackmail purposes.  The epitome of </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4516973</uri>
        <title>8 Tricks to Improve the Picture on Your New TV</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2078431372549019</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Technology, dmoz/Arts/Television/Guides, dmoz/Arts/Television/Schedule and Programming, dmoz/Arts/Television/Interactive</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>16</article_count>
        <total_article_count>16</total_article_count>
        <summary>Right now is one of the best times to buy a new TV. In early January, TV makers will announce their 2019 sets at CES, so all the 2018 set will be cheaper than usual as companies work to burn off their old inventory. And seeing as all those new, 2019 TVs won't start showing up in stores until March, at the earliest you've got a few months to enjoy your set without being envious of others. But you know what will make your TV even more enjoyable? These tricks for significantly improving its image qu</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4516729</uri>
        <title>Apple Beware: Samsung's Great Fall in China Was Swift </title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1137254901960785</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Technology, dmoz/Computers/Systems/Apple, dmoz/Computers/Hardware/Retailers, dmoz/Business/Chemicals/Biochemical</categories>
        <loc_country>China</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>10</article_count>
        <total_article_count>10</total_article_count>
        <summary>In five years, Samsung went from China's No. 1 to less than 1% market share By Timothy W. Martin Timothy W. Martin The Wall Street Journal BiographyTimothy W. Martin @timothywmartin Google+ Timothy.Martin@wsj.com Jan. 4, 2019 7:20 a.m. ET  SEOUL -- Apple Inc.'s AAPL 4.27% recently revealed stumble in China is an all-too-familiar story for smartphone rival Samsung Electronics Co.  Five years ago, the South Korean technology giant sat atop the Chinese market, selling nearly one of every five device</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4506731</uri>
        <title>Winds improve Delhi air; pollution likely to ease up</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.1137254901960785</sentiment>
        <categories>dmoz/Science/Environment/Air Quality, news/Environment, dmoz/Shopping/Home and Garden/Climate Control, dmoz/Science/Technology/Quality Engineering</categories>
        <loc_country>India</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>77</article_count>
        <total_article_count>77</total_article_count>
        <summary>New Delhi, Jan 4 (IANS) Despite adverse meteorological conditions, a sudden increase in wind speed improved the toxic air quality of the national capital to 'very poor' on Friday and as per the Met, it is likely to improve a few more notches over the next few days.  "Despite unfavourable meteorological conditions including a dense fog, the overall air quality in Delhi has improved from 'severe' to 'very poor' category due to an appreciable increase in wind speed (4.1 km/hr).  "It is likely to imp</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4511610</uri>
        <title>How A YouTube Yoga Channel Helped Me Get Over My Fear Of Working Out</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1294117647058823</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Health, dmoz/Society/Religion and Spirituality/Yoga</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>24</article_count>
        <total_article_count>24</total_article_count>
        <summary>Apparently, there's nothing my body loves more than starting a new year off by coming down with the flu. Last January, I stayed in bed for almost two weeks, and it did weird things to my head: I was sick and bored and actually angry at my body. I devoted so much headspace to feeling weak and pathetic that I started to give in to the fear that maybe I was a weak and pathetic person. Even when I started to regain my energy, I couldn't bring myself to hit the gym or even venture outside for a brisk,</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4516088</uri>
        <title>Opinion | A great first step to protect antibiotics for the future</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.06666666666666665</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Health, dmoz/Health/Pharmacy/Drugs and Medications, dmoz/Health/Animal/Drugs and Medications, dmoz/Society/Issues/Animal Welfare</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>11</article_count>
        <total_article_count>11</total_article_count>
        <summary>By Editorial Board January 1 at 4:58 PM  VERY PROMISING news about antibiotic use in farm animals has come from the Food and Drug Administration. The problem of resistance -- the tendency of bacteria to fight back against antibiotic drugs -- has been growing for decades, fueled by overuse and misuse of antibiotics in human health, as well as widespread and often indiscriminate use in farm animals. But new data shows the use of antibiotics in animal agriculture has taken a marked downward turn.  A</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4516664</uri>
        <title>Tainted drugs: When medicine makes patients sicker</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.03529411764705892</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Health, dmoz/Health/Pharmacy/Drugs and Medications, dmoz/Health/Teen Health/Drugs and Alcohol, dmoz/Shopping/Health/Home Tests</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>19</article_count>
        <total_article_count>19</total_article_count>
        <summary>This is a Kaiser Health News story.  The Food and Drug Administration is supposed to inspect all factories, foreign and domestic, that produce drugs for the U.S. market. But a KHN review of thousands of FDA documents -- inspection records, recalls, warning letters and lawsuits -- reveals how drugs that are poorly manufactured or contaminated can reach consumers.  Despite the jackhammer-like rhythm of a mechanical ventilator, Alicia Moreno had dozed off in a chair by her 1-year-old's hospital bed,</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4506674</uri>
        <title>How to start the Mediterranean diet (and stay on it)</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Health, dmoz/Health/Nutrition/Dietary Options, dmoz/Health/Weight Loss/Support Groups, dmoz/Health/Weight Loss/Articles</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>105</article_count>
        <total_article_count>105</total_article_count>
        <summary>Chat with us in Facebook Messenger. Find out what's happening in the world as it unfolds.  (CNN)A diet that's good for healthy weight loss? Check. One that reduces the risk for diabetes, high cholesterol, heart disease, stroke and some cancers? Check. A diet that strengthens bones, improves brain health and wards off dementia and depression? Check.  According to scientific research, that impossible wish list is fulfilled by a diet common to residents of 21 sun-soaked countries that surround the M</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4510078</uri>
        <title>Lawsuit filed against NJ facility over potential HIV exposure</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.1058823529411764</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Health, dmoz/Health/Medicine, dmoz/Health/Conditions and Diseases/Digestive Disorders, dmoz/Health/Public Health and Safety/Patient Safety</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>15</article_count>
        <total_article_count>15</total_article_count>
        <summary>Kemberly Richardson has the latest on a class-action lawsuit filed against a New Jersey surgery center.  More potential victims are joining a class-action lawsuit against a New Jersey surgery center that may have exposed more than 3,000 patients to HIV, hepatitis B and hepatitis C.  State health officials say patients who underwent procedures at the HealthPlus Surgery Center in Saddle Brook may have been exposed to bloodborne infections because of lapses in infection control procedures.  Attorney</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4510684</uri>
        <title>Why exercise alone won't save us</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1372549019607843</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Health, dmoz/Shopping/Health/Weight Loss, dmoz/Health/Weight Loss, dmoz/Health/Fitness/Advice and Guides</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>24</article_count>
        <total_article_count>24</total_article_count>
        <summary>Sedentary lifestyles are killing us - we need to build activity into our everyday lives, not just leave it for the gym. By Vybarr Cregan-Reid  This is the time of year when trainers are mined from under beds and gym kits are disinterred from the bottom drawer. Google searches relating to physical fitness peak in January. Many people even trawl the web to find out about "desk exercises" and "workouts on the go" in case they are too busy to use their new gym memberships.  Our relationship with exer</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4510920</uri>
        <title>With blood supplies 'dangerously low,' donors are offered H-E-B gift cards, pizza</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.05882352941176472</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Health, dmoz/Games/Board Games/Sports, dmoz/Science/Biology/Cryobiology</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>61</article_count>
        <total_article_count>61</total_article_count>
        <summary>Facing a "dangerously low" supply of blood to start the year, the South Texas Blood and Tissue Center is urging the public to donate blood -- and is promoting offers with H-E-B and others to help sweeten the deal.  The nonprofit organization attributed the low blood levels to declining donations over the holidays, coupled with several canceled blood drives that typically replenish supplies during the first month of the year.  Demand for blood tends to be the highest in January because many surger</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4505555</uri>
        <title>'Snowman' shape of distant Ultima revealed</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1450980392156862</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Science, dmoz/Science/Astronomy, dmoz/Science/Technology/Space, dmoz/Science/Astronomy/Solar System</categories>
        <loc_country>Greenland</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>637</article_count>
        <total_article_count>659</total_article_count>
        <summary>The ice world known as Ultima Thule has finally been revealed.  A new picture returned from Nasa's New Horizons spacecraft shows the little world to be two objects joined together - to give a look like a "snowman".  The US probe's images acquired as it approached Ultima hinted at the possibility of a double body, but the first detailed picture from Tuesday's close flyby confirms it.  New Horizons encountered Ultima 6.5 billion km from Earth.  The event set a record for the most distant ever explo</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4506353</uri>
        <title>'Super blood wolf moon' kicks off super year for eclipses</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1764705882352942</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Science, dmoz/Science/Astronomy/Solar System, dmoz/Science/Anomalies and Alternative Science/Anomalous Objects, dmoz/Science/Astronomy/Eclipses, Occultations and Transits</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>61</article_count>
        <total_article_count>61</total_article_count>
        <summary>Six eclipses will take to the sky in 2019, including one in just a few days and a total lunar eclipse that will turn the moon red later this month.  For sky watchers in parts of north Asia, the new year will begin with the moon taking a "bite" out of the sun a few weeks before the rest of us are treated to the spooky-sounding conjunction of celestial events known as a "super blood wolf moon."  Altogether there will six eclipses observable from planet Earth in 2019, including a total solar eclipse</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4506840</uri>
        <title>ISRO Gunning For SpaceX's Falcon 9, Working On Its Own Vertical Landing Reusable Rocket</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2078431372549019</sentiment>
        <categories>dmoz/Science/Technology, news/Science, dmoz/Business/Aerospace and Defense/Space, dmoz/Science/Technology/Space</categories>
        <loc_country>India</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>40</article_count>
        <total_article_count>40</total_article_count>
        <summary>India's usually low-profile space agency, ISRO, suddenly had the spotlight pointed at it after the success of the Mangalyaan Mars mission. And since then it has been constantly in the news - launching a record 104 satellites, testing the Crew Module on its biggest GSLV Mk3 rocket, testing the RLV (Reusable Launch Vehicle) and more recently about the Gaganyaan manned space mission.  Now, it intends to take on SpaceX. More specifically the company's Falcon 9 reusable rocket. According to a report i</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4504580</uri>
        <title>National Parks Getting Trashed During Government Shutdown</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.1450980392156863</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Science, dmoz/Recreation/Theme Parks, dmoz/Recreation/Theme Parks/Individual Parks, dmoz/Recreation/Theme Parks/Guides</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>55</article_count>
        <total_article_count>74</total_article_count>
        <summary>Filth spreads as overused restrooms and trash bins are locked, causing public health concerns.  Some National Parks are being overwhelmed by trash, vandalism, human feces and destructive off-roading while most personnel are gone during the government shutdown, according to reports from remaining workers and visitors.  "It's so heartbreaking. There is more trash and human waste and disregard for the rules than I've seen in my four years living here," Dakota Snider, 24, who works in California's Yo</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4510738</uri>
        <title>Leak on International Space Station blamed on 'botched repair job'</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.03529411764705881</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Science, dmoz/Business/Aerospace and Defense/Space, dmoz/Science/Technology/Space</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>10</article_count>
        <total_article_count>10</total_article_count>
        <summary>The commander of the International Space Station has confirmed that a leak in its space capsule was caused deliberately and could have had "severe" consequences for him and his crew.  The leak was detected by NASA officials in late August, when flight controllers on Earth noticed a dip in the air pressure of the ISS.  It was identified by the crew as coming from a two millimetre hole on a section of the Russian-made Soyuz space capsule.  Nasa said at the time the crew were "never in any danger", </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4505726</uri>
        <title>Popovich hopeful fans treat Leonard with 'kindness, respect'</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1137254901960785</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Games/Video Games/Browser Based, dmoz/Games/Hand-Eye Coordination/Booby-Trap, dmoz/Sports/Basketball/Professional</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>235</article_count>
        <total_article_count>235</total_article_count>
        <summary>SAN ANTONIO - On the eve of Kawhi Leonard's return to San Antonio to face the Spurs as a member of the Toronto Raptors, coach Gregg Popovich said Thursday he has no regrets about how last season's drama with the player pegged to be the face of the franchise for years to come played out.  "You move on in life," Popovich said. "We're not going to re-do what's happened in the past in any way, shape or form. It's of no consequence at this point, and it does not good to go backward and talk about this</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4504520</uri>
        <title>Roger Federer Struggles With Serena Williams's Serve. And Vice Versa.</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.3647058823529412</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Society/Politics/Federalism and Devolution, dmoz/Sports/Hockey/Bandy</categories>
        <loc_country>Australia</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Oceania</loc_continent>
        <article_count>328</article_count>
        <total_article_count>375</total_article_count>
        <summary>PERTH, Australia -- After nearly two decades of appearing alongside one another on billboards and in record books, Serena Williams and Roger Federer faced one another across a tennis court for the first time on Tuesday.  The incandescent stars, now both 37, finally aligned for the first time in a mixed doubles match between the United States and Switzerland at the Hopman Cup team event.  On the opening point, Williams pulled Federer wide to his forehand side with a sharply angled volley, then sen</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4503767</uri>
        <title>Thigh injury forces Rafael Nadal to withdraw from Brisbane International</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1215686274509804</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Arts/Online Writing/Drama, dmoz/Games/Dice/Fill or Bust, dmoz/Arts/Literature/Drama</categories>
        <loc_country>Australia</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Oceania</loc_continent>
        <article_count>77</article_count>
        <total_article_count>99</total_article_count>
        <summary>Jan. 2 (UPI) -- World No. 2 Rafael Nadal withdrew from the Brisbane International on Wednesday after an MRI showed a strain in his left thigh.  Nadal told reporters at a press conference ahead of the event that he wanted to play, but doctors explained the risk of further injury to his thigh should he participate.  "I did an MRI and it shows a small strain on my left thigh," Nadal told reporters. "I tried to play, I wanted to play, but recommendations from the doctors [said no].  "It's a small thi</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4506005</uri>
        <title>Kucherov, red-hot Lightning beat Kings 6-2 for 7th straight</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1607843137254903</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Games/Hand-Eye Coordination/Booby-Trap, dmoz/Games/Dice/Farkle, dmoz/Games/Board Games/Historical</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>29</article_count>
        <total_article_count>29</total_article_count>
        <summary>LOS ANGELES (AP) - The Tampa Bay Lightning got off to a strong start last season, only to lose momentum after Christmas.  They aren't about to let that happen again, as the Los Angeles Kings found out.  Nikita Kucherov had a goal and three assists as the Lightning kept steamrolling along, beating the Kings 6-2 on Thursday night for their seventh straight victory.  "This group has been together for quite a while, so we know what we're capable of," Tampa Bay forward Ryan Callahan said. "Make sure w</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4505513</uri>
        <title>Urban Meyer Passes the Reins to Ryan Day in His Final Locker Room Speech to His Team</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1607843137254903</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Sports/Bowling, dmoz/Sports/Bowling/Ten-Pin, dmoz/Sports/Bowling/Instructors</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>181</article_count>
        <total_article_count>197</total_article_count>
        <summary>After winning the Rose Bowl against the Washington Huskies, Urban Meyer seemed at peace with both his legacy at Ohio State and what he's been able to build and accomplish for the future. In his final locker room speech as Ohio State head coach, he addressed both of those ideas, while also passing the torch to Ryan Day.  Addressing his team he asked them to reflect on how they had faced adversity during the 2018 season, and how their fans and supporters had rallied around them.  "Never forget Buck</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4504314</uri>
        <title>Jets fire coach Bowles after third losing season</title>
        <event_date>2018-12-30</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.003921568627450966</sentiment>
        <categories>dmoz/Sports/Bowling, dmoz/Sports/Bowling/Ten-Pin, dmoz/Sports/Bowling/Instructors, news/Sports</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>143</article_count>
        <total_article_count>156</total_article_count>
        <summary>FLORHAM PARK, N.J. -- For the second time in four years, the New York Jets are in the market for a head coach.  Todd Bowles, who presided over one of the worst three-year stretches in franchise history, was fired Sunday evening in a long-anticipated move.  Ownership decided against a complete overhaul, opting to retain embattled general manager Mike Maccagnan, who was hired the same day as Bowles in 2015.  Maccagnan and Bowles were thought to be a tandem -- their contracts run concurrently -- but</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4506467</uri>
        <title>Social Media Has A Fit After So Many Black Head Coaches Got Fired After NFL Season (TWEETS)</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.06666666666666665</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Sports/Basketball/Coaching, dmoz/Health/Alternative/Coaching, dmoz/Business/Management/Consulting</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>25</article_count>
        <total_article_count>25</total_article_count>
        <summary>The Monday following the final week of the NFL season has forever been known as Black Monday, because teams usually make their decisions to either stay with their current head coach after a bad season or part ways with them after a bad season.  Black Monday took on a whole new meaning this week after eight head coaches got served their walking papers.  Among them were four African-American coaches, Marvin Lewis of the Cincinnati Bengals, Todd Bowles of the New York Jets, Vance Joseph of the Denve</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4506947</uri>
        <title>Clemson getting too many points in CFP title game</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1686274509803922</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Games/Video Games/Recreation, dmoz/Games/Play Groups, dmoz/Games/Video Games/Browser Based</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>165</article_count>
        <total_article_count>165</total_article_count>
        <summary>Trevor Lawrence's play at quarterback paired with a wildly talented defense has made Clemson into an even scarier version of the Deshaun Watson teams that went toe-to-toe with Alabama in two national championships.  Three things to know before betting on Clemson-Alabama:  1. The College Football Playoff national title game most people expected is a matchup of a pair of powerhouses squaring off in the CFP for the fourth consecutive season. In the 2015 National Championship, Clemson covered as a 6.</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507078</uri>
        <title>The Nuggets Break Record for Best Start in History After 117-113 win</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1294117647058823</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Games/Hand-Eye Coordination/Booby-Trap, dmoz/Games/Board Games/Historical</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>129</article_count>
        <total_article_count>129</total_article_count>
        <summary>Following a New Year's Day victory against the New York Knicks, The Denver Nuggets headed west to take on the Sacramento Kings. Their historic 117-113 victory puts the Nuggets at 25-11, which is the best start in franchise history.  "I think the reason why we're playing so well and winning at the level we're winning at is because guys truly care and love each other and that's really important for our locker room," said Nuggets coach Michael Malone.  The win was not as easy-coming as others as the</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507320</uri>
        <title>Sentry Tournament of Champions preview</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2627450980392156</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Sports/Golf/Golfers, dmoz/Sports/Golf/Organizations, dmoz/Sports/Golf/Tournaments and Events</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>107</article_count>
        <total_article_count>107</total_article_count>
        <summary>The first PGA Tour event of 2019 kicks off this week at the beautiful Kapalua Plantation Course on Maui. Here's everything you need to know.  With no disrespect to the fall swing, which gave us more intrigue than we could have expected -- the emergence of Cameron Champ, Charles Howell III's ending an 11-year winless drought, Brooks Koepka's ascent to No. 1 -- the annual Tournament of Champions in Hawaii still signifies like the beginning of the golf season. This week is when things really get sta</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4505916</uri>
        <title>Test cricket is great again. Thank the bowlers for it</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1294117647058823</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Computers/Programming/Software Testing, dmoz/Business/Electronics and Electrical/Safety and Compliance Testing, dmoz/Business/Textiles and Nonwovens/Test Facilities</categories>
        <loc_country>Australia</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Oceania</loc_continent>
        <article_count>513</article_count>
        <total_article_count>516</total_article_count>
        <summary>In 2018, the premier format was more competitive and evenly balanced than it has been for a while  If you are a cricket fan of my vintage, the festive spirit of this time of the year is further elevated by the rhapsodies of Test cricket from the southern hemisphere, Australia in particular. My own love story with the game began in 1977, with a small transistor radio painting pictures of a see-saw Test series between Bishan Bedi's Indians and Bobby Simpson's Australians that ended on the final day</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4503362</uri>
        <title>Pant debuts as Paine family babysitter</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2156862745098038</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Shopping/Health/Orthopedic, dmoz/Health/Senses/Touch and Sensation</categories>
        <loc_country>Australia</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Oceania</loc_continent>
        <article_count>48</article_count>
        <total_article_count>60</total_article_count>
        <summary>Sledging duel between Australia and India wicketkeepers in third Test at MCG delivers hilarious aftermath  The entertaining MCG sledging duel between the rival wicketkeepers has had a hilarious aftermath, with Rishabh Pant debuting as the Paine family babysitter.  Tim Paine's wife Bonnie posted a photo on social media of herself standing next to a beaming Pant, with her two young children either side of him and the caption "best babysitter".  The photo appears to have been taken at Tuesday's Kirr</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4519215</uri>
        <title>Mike Locksley explains why he didn't try to flip Alabama commits to Maryland</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1843137254901961</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Sports/Basketball/Coaching, dmoz/Sports/Football/American</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>5</article_count>
        <total_article_count>5</total_article_count>
        <summary>When Mike Locksley was hired as Maryland's next football coach, there was immediate speculation that he would try to flip DMV recruits, including those he guided to Alabama, to Maryland. But in an interview with AL.com's John Talty, Locksley explained why he refused to do so.  According to Talty, Locksley said he thought the right thing to do was try to leave them alone instead of trying to sway their decision. This is a different approach than current Georgia head coach Kirby Smart took after le</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4518141</uri>
        <title>Tua Tagovailoa is expecting 405 family members at national championship game</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.192156862745098</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Games/Video Games/Recreation, dmoz/Games/Play Groups, dmoz/Games/Play Groups/Europe</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>81</article_count>
        <total_article_count>81</total_article_count>
        <summary>Tua Tagovailoa is expecting 405 family members at national championship game  Ticket prices for the College Football Playoff National Championship game between No. 1 Alabama and No. 2 Clemson have plummeted compared with recent years. Some fans believe it's because the two teams are based significantly closer to the East Coast but will have to trek to Levi's Stadium in Santa Clara, California for Monday's game.  Although traveling to the West Coast is a disadvantage for some, it's particularly co</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4517348</uri>
        <title>Georgia Quarterback Justin Fields Set to Transfer to Ohio State</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.07450980392156858</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Sports/Track and Field, dmoz/Sports/Paintball/Fields, dmoz/Sports/Track and Field/Masters</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>51</article_count>
        <total_article_count>51</total_article_count>
        <summary>Georgia quarterback Justin Fields is transferring to Ohio State.  Sources told Eleven Warriors that Fields' "paperwork is in" and the five-star prospect will join the Buckeye football team.  The news was first reported by Jeremy Birmingham of Lettermen Row, who said Fields "is expected on campus with the Buckeyes later in the afternoon and set to move in this weekend ahead of the resumption of classes, clearing the way for him to participate in the offseason program and spring practice."  Ohio St</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4516984</uri>
        <title>3 Reasons the Seahawks Will Upset the Cowboys</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1607843137254903</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Games/Play Groups, dmoz/Games/Video Games/Browser Based, dmoz/Games/Board Games/Developers and Publishers</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>414</article_count>
        <total_article_count>356</total_article_count>
        <summary>After a disappointing 9-7 season in 2017 that was followed by the dissolution of the Legion of Boom, Pete Carroll and the Seahawks went into 2018 with extremely low expectations. But Russell Wilson and that ground game led them to a playoff berth against Dallas. With Dak Prescott and the Cowboys also coming in red hot, the Seahawks face an uphill battle this weekend. There is a way, however, to beat this revamped Cowboys roster.  Of the six quarterbacks the Cowboys lost to this season, only one (</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4515952</uri>
        <title>Perspective | Welcome to the Gymternet, where fantasy gymnastics reigns supreme</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2313725490196079</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Sports/Gymnastics, dmoz/Sports/Gymnastics/Artistic, dmoz/Sports/Gymnastics/Organizations</categories>
        <loc_country>Azerbaijan</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>10</article_count>
        <total_article_count>10</total_article_count>
        <summary>Maggie Nichols of Oklahoma was No. 1 on my fantasy gymnastics draft board. (Photo courtesy of OU Athletic Communications) By Emily Giambalvo Emily Giambalvo Reporter covering University of Maryland athletics Reporter January 3 at 12:49 PM  I spent New Year's Eve just as I have the last few years -- surrounded by a couple hundred people, some of whom I'll care deeply about in 2019.  They were 200 names on my computer screen, all NCAA gymnasts ranked for my fantasy draft.  By midnight, I had gone t</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4513505</uri>
        <title>It's official: NHL All-Star Game coming to St. Louis in 2020</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.08235294117647052</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Games/Video Games/Recreation, dmoz/Games/Video Games/Browser Based</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>36</article_count>
        <total_article_count>36</total_article_count>
        <summary>Little more than 12 months from now, the world's greatest hockey players will gather in downtown St. Louis for the NHL all-star weekend at Enterprise Center.  NHL Commissioner Gary Bettman made the official announcement on New Year's Day, during the second intermission of the nationally-televised Winter Classic game between the Boston Bruins and the Chicago Blackhawks.  "St. Louis was a great host for us for the Winter Classic we recently had there, and in the final analysis _ the total circumsta</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4510573</uri>
        <title>Danny Ainge: LeBron James May Be Taking 'Donald Trump Approach' with GOAT Remark</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2470588235294118</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Sports/Basketball/History, dmoz/Sports/Basketball/Science, dmoz/Sports/Basketball/Fan Pages</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>99</article_count>
        <total_article_count>99</total_article_count>
        <summary>LeBron James recently said that he felt winning a title with the Cleveland Cavaliers and beating the 73-win Golden State Warriors to do so made him the greatest player in NBA history.  And Boston Celtics president of basketball operations, Danny Ainge, was surprised by the comments.  "His career's not over," Ainge said during an interview on 98.5 The Sports Hub's Toucher &amp; Rich show (h/t Darren Hartwell of NBC Sports)." "I'd just like to -- why he's saying that, I don't know. Maybe he thinks that</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4509729</uri>
        <title>Antonio Brown Calls Ryan Clark An 'Uncle Tom' For Criticizing Him</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.0117647058823529</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Science/Anomalies and Alternative Science/Earth Lights</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>258</article_count>
        <total_article_count>258</total_article_count>
        <summary>The Pittsburgh Steelers have a very long offseason ahead of them and it has less to do with Le'Veon Bell and much more to do with Antonio Brown.  The two sides have been at odds ever since a scathing report revealed that the star WR was actually suspended for Week 17 for conduct detrimental to the team and it has only gotten worse in the days after.  Former Pittsburgh Steelers star Ryan Clark chimed in on the situation, stating it's time for the franchise to move forward.  "When it comes to just </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4509682</uri>
        <title>Dear NFL, please force the Raiders to be on 'Hard Knocks' next season</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.0117647058823529</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Business/Education and Training/Team Building, dmoz/Sports/Paintball/Teams, dmoz/Computers/Robotics/Competitions</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>10</article_count>
        <total_article_count>10</total_article_count>
        <summary>The 2018 NFL regular season has come to a close, which means it's time to focus on the most important question of the offseason. No, we're not talking about where Le'Veon Bell will sign, we're talking about which team will be on HBO's "Hard Knocks."  ProFootball Talk's Michael David Smith has already done the work and figured out the five teams that can't refuse to be on the program next year. Those five teams are the San Francisco 49ers, New York Giants, Detroit Lions, Washington Redskins and Oa</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4508943</uri>
        <title>Pier 64 restaurant owned by Craig Bellamy closes down</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.1529411764705882</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Sports/Basketball/Coaching, dmoz/Health/Alternative/Coaching, dmoz/Sports/Korfball/Clubs</categories>
        <loc_country>United Kingdom</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Europe</loc_continent>
        <article_count>55</article_count>
        <total_article_count>55</total_article_count>
        <summary>Get What's On updates directly to your inboxSubscribeSee our privacy noticeMore newslettersThank you for subscribingWe have more newslettersShow meSee our privacy noticeCould not subscribe, try again laterInvalid Email  The high-end restaurant Pier 64 in Penarth has closed as the company prepares to go into liquidation.  The restaurant in Penarth Marina describes itself as a wine bar and steakhouse and is owned by former Wales footballer Craig Bellamy.  Its website says the venue is currently clo</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4517693</uri>
        <title>REPORT: Two UCLA Boosters Want Rick Pitino and He's Interested in the Job</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1215686274509804</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Sports/Basketball/Coaching, dmoz/Health/Alternative/Coaching, dmoz/Business/Management/Consulting</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>13</article_count>
        <total_article_count>13</total_article_count>
        <summary>When Rick Pitino was fired in 2017 following some severe allegations of bribing recruits to come to the University of Lousiville (among other sordid details), many believed that the legendary coach would never again roam a college basketball sideline, Well, those days may be quickly coming to an end.  Recent reports have surfaced stating that two top athletic boosters at UCLA are actively trying to lure Pitino, who recently began coaching in Greece, to Westwood to succeed recently fired head coac</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4517347</uri>
        <title>Jamaican teen confessed to killing 12-yo in gang hunt, court told</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.09019607843137256</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Games/Video Games/Browser Based, dmoz/Games/Board Games/Developers and Publishers, dmoz/Business/Arts and Entertainment/Gaming</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>18</article_count>
        <total_article_count>18</total_article_count>
        <summary>A Jamaican undocumented immigrant has confessed to the fatal shooting of a 12-year-old boy in Connecticut, according to court documents.  Eighteen-year-old Tajay Chambers, who is reportedly a citizen of Jamaica, was presented in Superior Court on murder and other charges last Thursday and 16-year-old Alexander Bolanos was arraigned the day prior on charges including conspiracy to commit murder. Both are charged in the December 18 drive-by shooting of 12-year-old Clinton Howell.  Both were ordered</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4514114</uri>
        <title>2019 NFL Mock Draft: Jaguars trade up for QB, Raiders take two receivers in Round 1</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1294117647058823</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Sports/Football/American</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>14</article_count>
        <total_article_count>14</total_article_count>
        <summary>There should be plenty of interest in trading up for Dwayne Haskins by the time April rolls around  The 2018 regular season has been put to bed, so now it's officially 2019 NFL Draft season. For the 20 teams that missed the playoffs, the focus turns toward upgrading rosters through free agency, the draft ... and trades.  That's right, the T-word. Since there's a 0.0 percent chance the top 20 picks as they stand now will be with the exact same teams by the time Day 1 of the draft is a wrap, why wo</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4505063</uri>
        <title>Herbert sparks Oregon past MSU in Redbox Bowl</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.09019607843137245</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Sports/Bowling, dmoz/Sports/Bowling/Ten-Pin, dmoz/Sports/Bowling/Candlepin Bowling</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>31</article_count>
        <total_article_count>51</total_article_count>
        <summary>Justin Herbert did just enough to keep his streak intact for consecutive games with a touchdown pass. Make it an impressive 28 and counting for Oregon's quarterback, the longest active streak in the nation among FBS schools.  That it turned out to be the Ducks lone score in their 7-6 win over Michigan State in the Redbox Bowl only emphasized why coach Mario Cristobal was smiling after Herbert's decision earlier this month to bypass the NFL draft.  Herbert shook off a sluggish day and threw a 28-y</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4511319</uri>
        <title>Amir Khan To Reportedly Fight Terence Crawford At Madison Square Garden</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.04313725490196074</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Sports/Team Spirit/Fight Songs, dmoz/Sports/Boxing, dmoz/Sports/Boxing/Fan Pages</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>28</article_count>
        <total_article_count>28</total_article_count>
        <summary>Amir Khan's next bout has almost been finalised after reports suggest that he will fight Terence Crawford.  Unnamed sources have told Boxing Scene that the 32-year-old Bolton-born boxer wants to challenge for the 31-year-old American's WBO Welterweight Championship at Madison Square Garden in New York City on 20th April.  According to the publication, Khan has 'informed' promoter Eddie Hearn that his next opponent should be Crawford, not Kell Brook.  It is expected that an official announcement f</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4510757</uri>
        <title>Grading the deal: Phillies pay up for David Robertson</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2156862745098038</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Sports/Baseball/Major League</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>177</article_count>
        <total_article_count>177</total_article_count>
        <summary>He's not named Bryce Harper or Manny Machado, but David Robertson is a strong addition to the contender that Philadelphia is trying to build.  For the second consecutive year, the deep freeze of winter is icing what was once a hot stove. And for the second consecutive year, the only players signing lucrative contracts are relief pitchers. The Phillies' latest transaction was not signing Bryce Harper or Manny Machado, to whom they have both been linked, but reliever David Robertson on a two-year, </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4505606</uri>
        <title>Is Man United's resurgence for real or just temporary?</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.3019607843137255</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports</categories>
        <loc_country>United Kingdom</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Europe</loc_continent>
        <article_count>561</article_count>
        <total_article_count>595</total_article_count>
        <summary>Is Manchester United's uptick in form due to caretaker manager Ole Gunnar Solskjaer's magic wand or simply a product of the fixture list?  Manchester United has its fans believing again. Two weeks after Jose Mourinho was fired, the club is now enjoying its best run of the season, with three consecutive, convincing wins under the guidance of caretaker manager Ole Gunnar Solskjaer.  United has outscored its three opponents-all bottom-half-of-the-table sides, it must be said-by a combined 12-3 score</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4505908</uri>
        <title>Deadline passes without Russian turnover of data to WADA</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.1294117647058823</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Sports/Organizations</categories>
        <loc_country>Russia</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Europe</loc_continent>
        <article_count>106</article_count>
        <total_article_count>109</total_article_count>
        <summary>In this Sept 20, 2018, photo, Yuri Ganus, head of the Russian Anti-Doping Agency, leaves an office building in Moscow. (ALEXANDER ZEMLIANICHENKO / AP)  The deadline for Russia to turn over samples and other data from its Moscow anti-doping lab has passed, leaving the World Anti-Doping Agency (WADA) to decide whether to reinstate the ban it had lifted in September.  WADA's decision to declare the Russian Anti-Doping Agency compliant came with the requirement that it turn over data and samples by D</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4506085</uri>
        <title>Report: Barcelona has deal to sign PSG's Rabiot</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1529411764705881</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Home/Moving and Relocating, dmoz/Home/Moving and Relocating/Moving, dmoz/Business/Business Services/Signage</categories>
        <loc_country>Spain</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Europe</loc_continent>
        <article_count>31</article_count>
        <total_article_count>31</total_article_count>
        <summary>Barcelona are closing in on the signing of Paris Saint-Germain midfielder Adrien Rabiot.  Barcelona are closing in on the signing of Paris Saint-Germain midfielder Adrien Rabiot, with the last few details being ironed out before the transfer becomes official.  Rabiot was expected to join Barcelona after recently being exiled from the PSG team for confirming that he would not sign a new contract with the French champions.  According to Paris United, Barcelona and Rabiot have reached an agreement o</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507049</uri>
        <title>Kawhi Leonard says 'it's going to be fun' playing against the Spurs in San Antonio</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1607843137254903</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Games/Hand-Eye Coordination/Booby-Trap, dmoz/Games/Dice/Farkle, dmoz/Games/Tile Games/Spectrangle</categories>
        <loc_country>Canada</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>116</article_count>
        <total_article_count>121</total_article_count>
        <summary>Thursday night, Toronto Raptors superstar small forward Kawhi Leonard will make his much-anticipated return to a place he called home for seven years.  Kawhi Leonard and the Raptors will be in San Antonio taking on the Spurs, and the two-time Defensive Player of the Year says "it's going to be fun" playing against his old team, according to Jabari Young of The Atheltic:  Kawhi Leonard was a two-time All-Star with the Spurs, won two Defensive Player of the Year awards, and won the 2014 Finals MVP </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507422</uri>
        <title>Wolves sign David Wang on four-and-a-half-year deal</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2470588235294118</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Sports/Soccer/Statistics, dmoz/Business/Financial Services/Loans, dmoz/Business/Financial Services/College Financing</categories>
        <loc_country>Spain</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Europe</loc_continent>
        <article_count>13</article_count>
        <total_article_count>13</total_article_count>
        <summary>Wolves sign David Wang on four-and-a-half-year deal  Last Updated: 01/01/19 6:59pm  Wolves have signed 18-year-old David Wang on a four-and-a-half-year deal from Spanish fourth-tier team Jumilla B (Estudiantes).  Wang, who speaks Spanish, Chinese and English, took a tour of Molineux before jetting out to Portugal where he will spend the rest of the season on loan at Sporting CP.  The right-footed winger becomes Wolves' first signing of the January transfer window.  He grew up in Cuenca, Spain bac</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507749</uri>
        <title>Jan Kocian wants Yemen to dream of big victories at 2019 Asian Cup</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2549019607843137</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Sports, dmoz/Sports/Soccer/Competitions, dmoz/Sports/Soccer/Statistics, dmoz/Sports/Soccer/CONMEBOL</categories>
        <loc_country>United Arab Emirates</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>73</article_count>
        <total_article_count>77</total_article_count>
        <summary>The Slovak manager aware his side face tough test to get out of Group D with Iran their first opponent  Yemen manager Jan Kocian says the Asian Cup debutants are dreaming of upsetting the more established teams at this month's tournament in the UAE.  The Middle Eastern side, the lowest-ranked team in the competition at 135th in the world, begin their Group D campaign next Monday against Iran, the continent's top team at 29th, in Abu Dhabi.  Following that, Yemen take on Iraq in Sharjah on January</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4503702</uri>
        <title>Ariana Grande 'refuses Damehood out of respect for Manchester Bombing victims'</title>
        <event_date>2018-12-30</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.09019607843137245</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>88</article_count>
        <total_article_count>106</total_article_count>
        <summary>Ariana Grande has turned down the honour of Damehood in the New Year Honours list in respect for grieving families of the Manchester Arena bomb victims, it has been claimed.  The singer was reportedly put up for the prestigious gong for her response to the devastating attack that left 22 dead at her gig in May 2017.  In the weeks that followed Ariana, 25, returned to the UK to meet victims' families and youngsters recovering in hospital. She also organised charity concert One Love Manchester whic</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507455</uri>
        <title>This New Netflix Cleaning Show Will Make You Want To Throw Your Whole House Away</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2627450980392156</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>24</article_count>
        <total_article_count>27</total_article_count>
        <summary>We're just here for the internet reactions to this new Netflix show, TBH  Perhaps you've heard of the bestselling book, The Life-Changing Magic of Tidying Up? If so, and you've read it and applied the wisdom of the author, Marie Kondo, to your home and your life -- congratulations.  If you'd rather skip the book and head straight for the new Netflix series that helps people clean their cluttered-ass houses, you're not alone. Keep reading.  Full disclosure: if you're looking to take part in the sc</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507479</uri>
        <title>Gallery demands back Nazi-stolen painting</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.2235294117647059</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Society/History/By Time Period, dmoz/Arts/Visual Arts/Painting</categories>
        <loc_country>Italy</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Europe</loc_continent>
        <article_count>33</article_count>
        <total_article_count>33</total_article_count>
        <summary>An art gallery in Florence has demanded the return of a painting stolen by Nazi troops in 1943 and now in the hands of a German family.  Uffizi Gallery head Eike Schmidt said the German government had a "moral duty" to help bring the artwork Vase of Flowers back to the museum.  Dutch master Jan van Huysum painted the still life and it was first displayed in Florence in 1824.  But German troops stole the work in 1943 as they retreated north.  Intermediaries for the unidentified family have demande</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507557</uri>
        <title>Get Started on Your 2019 Reading List With All These New Sci-Fi and Fantasy Books</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1843137254901961</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Society/History, dmoz/Society/History/By Time Period, dmoz/Society/Issues</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>5</article_count>
        <total_article_count>5</total_article_count>
        <summary>It's 2019! If one of your New Year's resolutions is to "read more sci-fi and fantasy," we've got all kinds of great suggestions to get you started. And if that isn't on your list of ways to self-improve, you just might get inspired to add it after seeing all the new books that January has to offer.  The author's latest installment in her Phillip K. Dick Award-nominated Jurisdiction Series is set in the lawless "Gonebeyond Space," where one determined fleet inquisitor finds himself in a fight agai</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4509356</uri>
        <title>Edgar Hilsenrath, 92, Writer of Unvarnished Holocaust Novels, Dies</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.01960784313725494</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Society/Religion and Spirituality/Judaism, dmoz/Society/Politics/Fascism</categories>
        <loc_country>Germany</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Europe</loc_continent>
        <article_count>12</article_count>
        <total_article_count>12</total_article_count>
        <summary>Edgar Hilsenrath, a German-Jewish survivor of Nazi persecution who unsentimentally stoked the embers of the Holocaust with brutally satirical autobiographical novels, died on Sunday in Wittlich, Germany. He was 92.  His death was announced by his French publisher, Le Tripode.  Mr. Hilsenrath finished his first novel, "Night," after emigrating to New York in 1951 as a refugee from war-torn Europe. (He lived in New Yorkuntil 1975.) Published in English in 1964, the novel was inspired by his dehuman</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4509651</uri>
        <title>Rock icon Dr. Hook dies in Daytona Beach</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.08235294117647063</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Arts/Music/Styles, dmoz/Arts/Music/Marching, dmoz/Health/Alternative/Naturopathy</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>15</article_count>
        <total_article_count>15</total_article_count>
        <summary>If there's a rock 'n' roll heaven, its heck o a band now has a heck of a distinctive vocalist.  Ray Sawyer, the lead singer of Dr. Hook &amp; The Medicine Show, died in his adopted hometown of Daytona Beach, his wife announced on Facebook. He was 81.  "My heart is broken," Linda Sawyer posted on Monday. "Ray passed away this morning peacefully in his sleep. We thank you all for your continued support and prayers. Ray loved you all."  Sawyer will be remembered by millions of people as the scruffy fron</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4509899</uri>
        <title>Bohemian Rhapsody Blu-ray To Include Full Live Aid Performance</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2862745098039217</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Arts/Movies</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>54</article_count>
        <total_article_count>54</total_article_count>
        <summary>I didn't have particularly high hopes for Bohemian Rhapsody, but despite its torturous production, it turned out way better than I expected. My favorite sequence by far was the film's climactic recreation of Queen's iconic performance during 1985's Live Aid. This was perhaps the highlight of the band's career, showcasing Freddie Mercury at his most potent and powerful. So, the news that the upcoming home video release will include a full recreation of it is good to hear as far as I'm concerned.  </summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4510121</uri>
        <title>In the Race for Content, Hollywood Is Buying Up Hit Podcasts</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.07450980392156858</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Arts/Television, dmoz/Arts/Television/Cable Television, dmoz/Arts/Television/Guides</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>8</article_count>
        <total_article_count>8</total_article_count>
        <summary>The film mogul Darryl F. Zanuck was among the skeptics in the years before networks started broadcasting shows seven nights a week. "Television won't be able to hold on to any market it captures after the first six months," he infamously predicted. "People will soon get tired of staring at a plywood box every night."  To make sure that television sets would become something more than ungainly appliances, entertainment executives of the late 1940s and early 1950s went in search of programming. And</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4511154</uri>
        <title>The Stars Align: Ten Broadway People to Watch in 2019!</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1450980392156862</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Arts/Performing Arts, dmoz/Arts/Performing Arts/Theatre</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>25</article_count>
        <total_article_count>25</total_article_count>
        <summary>2018 is over and we can't help but look ahead to the 2019 Broadway season, which is bound to be filled with countless star-making (and star-preserving) performances. Who should you keep your eye on as the spring season begins and awards season approaches?  Before he presides over the Moulin Rogue as eccentric frontman Harold Zidler next summer, the six-time Tony nominee will step in as Alfred P. Doolittle in My Fair Lady. With a little bit of luck will see just as much Burstein in seasons to come</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4505824</uri>
        <title>Kader Khan: The man behind the legend</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.04313725490196074</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Arts/Performing Arts/Acting, dmoz/Arts/Movies, dmoz/Arts/Movies/Filmmaking</categories>
        <loc_country>Afghanistan</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>303</article_count>
        <total_article_count>303</total_article_count>
        <summary>Bollywood veterans remember their friend and colleague who passed away at the age of 81.  Veteran actor Kader Khan passed away on Monday evening in Canada after fighting Progressive Supranuclear Palsy, a degenerative disease, for many years. He was 81. His last rites will be performed in Canada.  Khan was not only an outstanding actor but also a prolific writer, having written dialogues for a number of films and screenplays for more than 40 years and was associated with many of Amitabh Bachchan's</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4508165</uri>
        <title>After Katrina's Exit, Sara Ali Khan Reportedly Roped In Opposite Varun Dhawan In A Dance Film</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Arts/Movies, dmoz/Arts/Movies/Filmmaking, dmoz/Arts/Movies/Organizations</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>19</article_count>
        <total_article_count>19</total_article_count>
        <summary>Bollywood actress Sara Ali Khan ended the year 2018 with a bang. She made a debut on Koffee With Karan and took everyone by surprise with her graceful answers and poised nature.  She won people's hearts during Simmba promotions and proved she's down to earth just like all of us. And then her movies arrived with Kedarnath and Simmba. The actress created fireworks with her performance and the audience has welcomed her into the world of Bollywood.  With New Year, Sara Ali Khan has more films in her </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4508192</uri>
        <title>Janhvi Kapoor opens up on mother Sridevi's untimely demise | Bollywood Bubble</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1058823529411765</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Arts/Movies</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>15</article_count>
        <total_article_count>19</total_article_count>
        <summary>During 2018, legendary actress Sridevi passed away under unfortunate circumstances. The untimely and tragic death of Sridevi really shook the industry and left a big void.  Janhvi Kapoor, soon after her mother's death, had her first release 'Dhadak'. The film was the official remake of Marathi film 'Sairat' and was directed by Shashank Khaitan. 'Dhadak' received positive reviews from the critics and did decent business at the box office.  Now, Janhvi Kapoor has opened up during an interview to Fi</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4511873</uri>
        <title>Simmba (Simba) vs Temper box office collection: Ranveer Singh achieves what Jr NTR could not</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1686274509803922</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Arts/Movies, dmoz/Arts/Movies/Organizations, dmoz/Arts/Movies/Theory and Criticism</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>82</article_count>
        <total_article_count>82</total_article_count>
        <summary>Jr NTR's Temper could attain its hit status in its lifetime, but its Hindi remake - Simmba (Simba) achieved it in just 5 days with its collection reaching Rs 124.54 crore net at the domestic box office.  Jr NTR's Temper could attain its hit status in its lifetime, but its Hindi remake - Simmba (Simba) achieved it in just 5 days with its collection reaching Rs 124.54 crore nett at the domestic box office.  Temper was one of the most hyped Telugu movies of 2015 and a lot of aspects including Jr NTR</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4512164</uri>
        <title>URI: Vicky Kaushal starrer to reminiscence Hollywood's Zero Dark Thirty!</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.09019607843137245</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Arts/Movies, dmoz/Arts/Movies/Education, dmoz/Arts/Movies/Theory and Criticism</categories>
        <loc_country>India</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>27</article_count>
        <total_article_count>27</total_article_count>
        <summary>Mumbai: One of the most anticipated films of 2019, RSVP's URI has got everyone excited to witness the events took place in the history of the Indian army. As the war drama brings to screen the reality behind the surgical strikes on 11th Jan, URI draws parallels to the international hit 'Zero Dark Thirty'.  Based on the coveted surgical strikes of 2016, Aditya Dhar's directorial URI traces the heroic triumph of the Indian army against the militant bases of Pakistan. For the first time in the histo</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4515969</uri>
        <title>'Bringing your family together is the best feeling'</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2784313725490195</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Arts/Movies</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>35</article_count>
        <total_article_count>35</total_article_count>
        <summary>Sara Ali Khan speaks to us about her early success, family ties and the road ahead.  Sara Ali Khan has firmly based her feet in Bollywood with two back-to-back film releases. Many may credit these feats to nepotism or even call it beginners luck, but Sara openly admits to having certain privileges that rocket launched her into Bollywood. It is this unabashed acceptance of her life and all that surrounds it, makes one believe that she is cut out of a different mould. Her acting skills have the aud</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4505189</uri>
        <title>Kanye West Reaffirms His Support for Donald Trump in the New Year</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1215686274509804</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>110</article_count>
        <total_article_count>135</total_article_count>
        <summary>The rapper is standing behind the president -- and he once again teased a possible run for office in the future  Kanye West kicked off the New Year of 2019 by reaffirming his support for President Donald Trump.  The rapper, who visited the White House last year, issued a series of short tweets on Tuesday afternoon that put his focus back on politics after he had publicly backed away from sharing his opinions.  West unexpectedly tweeted, "Trump all day."  He then followed that up by saying, "Just </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4505549</uri>
        <title>Single winner takes $425M Mega Millions jackpot</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.3725490196078431</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Arts/Television/Tickets For Shows, dmoz/Games/Gambling/Lotteries, dmoz/Shopping/Entertainment/Tickets</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>68</article_count>
        <total_article_count>76</total_article_count>
        <summary>WATCH Hopefuls line up as Mega Millions jackpot balloons to $425M  One person in New York will be ringing in 2019 with a whole lot of cash.  There was one big winner in Tuesday's $425 million Mega Millions jackpot drawing, the eighth-largest in jackpot in the game's history.  The winning numbers were: 34-44-57-62-70 with a Mega Ball of 14.  The winning ticket for the jackpot was purchased in New York, but buyers in Ohio, South Carolina and Texas also walked away with big prizes.  The exact locati</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4509869</uri>
        <title>'The fraud of socialism': Liz Cheney rips progressives in preview of House GOP attack plan</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.04313725490196085</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Arts/Movies, dmoz/Arts/Movies/Filmmaking</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>32</article_count>
        <total_article_count>32</total_article_count>
        <summary>Rep. Liz Cheney (R-Wyo.) talks during the first session of the 116th Congress on Thursday. (Chip Somodevilla/Getty Images) By Eli Rosenberg Eli Rosenberg General assignment reporter covering national and breaking news January 4 at 5:35 AM  Republican congresswoman Liz Cheney, a daughter of former vice president Richard B. Cheney, delivered a Trumpism-inflected speech to nominate Kevin McCarthy to be speaker of the House on Thursday, telegraphing the Republican strategy as the party moves forward </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4510732</uri>
        <title>Perspective | Carolyn Hax: An old flame and fears of getting burned</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.0117647058823529</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Society/Sexuality/Sexual Addiction, dmoz/Health/Addictions/Internet, dmoz/Society/Relationships/Marriage</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>5</article_count>
        <total_article_count>5</total_article_count>
        <summary>By Carolyn Hax Carolyn Hax Advice columnist Advice columnist January 1 at 11:59 PM  Dear Carolyn: I rejected "Sam" years ago in favor of "Aaron." Aaron and I are newly divorced -- initiated by me -- after 25 years of marriage and three kids.  Sam has been alienated from his wife for many years and moved out five years ago at her insistence. Sam initiated divorce proceedings, but they ultimately stalled and Sam and "Gina" remain married.  Sam says he stays in the marriage for the sake of their onl</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4511551</uri>
        <title>Pegi Young, Bridge School Co-Founder and Neil Young's Ex-Wife, Dead at 66</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.0117647058823529</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Science/Technology/Structural Engineering, dmoz/Arts/Writers Resources/Young Writers</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>40</article_count>
        <total_article_count>40</total_article_count>
        <summary>Pegi Young, a singer-songwriter who was married to Neil Young for 36 years, died Tuesday after a yearlong battle with cancer. She was 66. "[She] passed away surrounded by her friends and family in her native California," reads a short statement on her official Instagram account. "We request that the families' privacy be respected at this time."  Young was working as a waitress at a diner near Neil Young's ranch when they met in the mid-Seventies. "Never saw a woman look finer," Neil Young wrote i</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4512067</uri>
        <title>Tucker Carlson Blames Higher-Earning Women For 'Men In Decline'</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.1058823529411764</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Health/Women's Health/Smoking</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>38</article_count>
        <total_article_count>38</total_article_count>
        <summary>"Study after study has shown that when men make less than women, women generally don't want to marry them."  Fox News host Tucker Carlson on Wednesday lamented about what his show's chyron described as "men in decline." During one segment, he claimed there was "more drug and alcohol abuse" and "higher incarceration rates" in areas where women earn more money than their male counterparts.  Carlson -- whose show lost sponsors in December after he said immigrants make America "dirtier" -- proclaimed</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4515745</uri>
        <title>Changing face: how Nicole Kidman gets under the skin in Destroyer</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.05098039215686279</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Arts/Movies, dmoz/Arts/Movies/Filmmaking, dmoz/Arts/Movies/Genres</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>13</article_count>
        <total_article_count>13</total_article_count>
        <summary>As a hard-boiled detective with a radically altered face, the Oscar-winner's latest role is getting heralded as a major transformation but it's far more than stunt casting  The marketing for Karyn Kusama's sun-dried Californian cop thriller Destroyer has leaned heavily on the supposedly drastic change of pace - and face - it represents for its very famous leading lady. "Nothing Nicole Kidman has done in her career can prepare you for Destroyer," blares the leading pull-quote on the film's posters</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4516484</uri>
        <title>Eminem's daughter Hailie is an Instagram star with 1.3M followers</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.3333333333333333</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>19</article_count>
        <total_article_count>19</total_article_count>
        <summary>Hailie Scott Mathers, daughter of Detroit trailer park rapper Marhsall "Eminem" Mathers, is doing remarkably well considering nearly two decades ago her father rapped about murdering her mom, Kimberly Scott.  In spite of her father's fame and the songs her wrote about her, Hailie, now 23, has long managed to avoid the spotlight, instead focusing on school and eventually graduating from Michigan State University where she studied psychology.  But all of that is about to change.  Hailie has also ga</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4508575</uri>
        <title>Jada Pinkett Smith and Will Smith don't celebrate wedding anniversary</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1058823529411765</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Society/Relationships/Marriage</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>21</article_count>
        <total_article_count>21</total_article_count>
        <summary>They tied the knot on New Year's Eve in 1997.  But Jada Pinkett Smith has revealed that she and husband Will Smith don't celebrate their wedding anniversary any more.  The 47-year-old explained in the latest episode of her Red Table Talk series on Facebook Watch that the couple consider themselves 'life partners' and they often spend December 31 apart.  No big deal: They tied the knot on New Year's Eve in 1997. But Jada Pinkett Smith has revealed that she and husband Will Smith don't celebrate th</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507705</uri>
        <title>Ariana Grande Drops 'Thank U, Next' Outtakes, Says '7 Rings' Will Be Her Next Single</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Recreation/Humor/Relationships</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>99</article_count>
        <total_article_count>99</total_article_count>
        <summary>Ariana Grande continues to drop more content from the epic homage-filled video for her hit "Thank U, Next." The singer shared a blooper reel and deleted scene from the visual at midnight Thursday (Jan. 3).  The four-minute video begins with the cut segment, a re-creation of a famous Legally Blonde scene with Jennifer Coolidge. Grande acts as her lawyer, totally nailing Elle Woods' sassy demeanor and all-pink outfit.  Then come the bloopers: Ariana forgetting her lines, Troye Sivan getting slammed</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507326</uri>
        <title>Justin Bieber's face tattoo finally revealed</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2078431372549019</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Arts/Bodyart, dmoz/Arts/Bodyart/Tattoo, dmoz/Arts/Bodyart/Schools and Instruction</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>54</article_count>
        <total_article_count>54</total_article_count>
        <summary>Canadian pop star Justin Bieber has finally showed off his latest tattoo -- and it's tiny.  On Jan. 1, celebrity tattoo artist JonBoy posted a close-up photo of Bieber on Instagram revealing his eyebrow ink alongside a heartfelt caption. The portrait shows the word "grace" written in cursive above the 24-year-old's right eyebrow, a design Bieber has kept private until now.  View this post on Instagram  "2018 was a lot of work for me. Both in tattooing and inner work I thought I would never have t</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4505407</uri>
        <title>Tiffany Haddish tells PETA she will wear fur until police 'stop killing black people'</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1058823529411765</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Recreation/Humor/Jokes</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>82</article_count>
        <total_article_count>93</total_article_count>
        <summary>Tiffany Haddish seems to be ready to protect social injustice and the police-involved shootings of Black folks in a very unusual way... but animals lovers are not here for it.  The comedian took to her Instagram page following a show at The Comedy Store in Los Angeles and informed her 4.4 million followers that a fan had given her a fur coat. As such, she claimed she's going to wear fur "every day" until police stop killing Black people.  -- Floyd Mayweather bags $9 million in 2 minutes with Tens</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4509320</uri>
        <title>Almost half of Britons want Prince Charles to give throne to William</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.08235294117647052</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Society/Genealogy/Royalty, dmoz/Society/Politics/Monarchy</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>36</article_count>
        <total_article_count>40</total_article_count>
        <summary>Almost half of the British public believe Prince Charles should stand aside and let his eldest son William become the next king, polling shows.  The survey by BMG Research on behalf of The Independent found 46 per cent of Britons want the first in line to the throne to abdicate immediately to allow the Duke of Cambridge to take the throne.  Meanwhile, just 20 per cent of those surveyed think the Prince of Wales's wife, Camilla, Duchess of Cornwall, should take the title of queen should he become </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4510693</uri>
        <title>China Box Office Growth Slows to 9% in 2018, Hits $8.9 Billion</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1607843137254903</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Arts and Entertainment, dmoz/Arts/Movies, dmoz/Arts/Movies/Filmmaking, dmoz/Arts/Movies/Cultures and Groups</categories>
        <loc_country>China</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>5</article_count>
        <total_article_count>5</total_article_count>
        <summary>China's total box office revenue grew 9% in 2018 to $8.87 billion (RMB60.98 billion). But the rate of expansion was slower rate than the year before, when it rose 13.5%, state media and government reports said. Nevertheless, the country met its government-set 2018 box office target of RMB60 billion yuan in ticket sales on December 29.  Chinese-language films brought in $5.53 billion (RMB37.8 billion) in 2018, making up 62% of the total box office, the official Xinhua news agency said, citing data</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4506058</uri>
        <title>'Sin tax' doubles the cost of alcohol overnight in Qatar</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.01960784313725494</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Health/Addictions, dmoz/Health/Addictions/Substance Abuse, dmoz/Health/Specific Substances/Alcoholic Beverages</categories>
        <loc_country>Iran</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>25</article_count>
        <total_article_count>29</total_article_count>
        <summary>Doha is the capital of the State of Qatar.Kamran Jebreili / AP file  Qatar welcomed the new year by implementing a 100 percent tax on alcohol, doubling prices overnight and sending the cost of a 12-pack of beer jumping to $78.  The increase has been branded a "sin tax" by some residents of the wealthy Gulf state as it targets products widely prohibited under Islamic law.  It was introduced by Qatar's General Authority of Customs on Jan. 1, and applies to tobacco products, energy drinks and pork -</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4506713</uri>
        <title>'Like It Was Christmas All Year:' GOP Succeeded in Making 2018 Yet Another Year the Rich Got Richer</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.06666666666666665</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Business/Accounting, dmoz/Business/Accounting/Tax Negotiation and Representation, dmoz/Home/Personal Finance/Tax Preparation</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>89</article_count>
        <total_article_count>89</total_article_count>
        <summary>With year two of Republicans' Tax Cuts and Jobs Act (TCJA) now underway and the party touting the $1.5 trillion tax plan's supposed successes, critics of the unpopular law are spotlighting the party's broken promises and saying the so-called tax scam merely helped to make 2018 another year of bloated corporate profits and enriching the already wealthy.  In fact, the wealthy were "celebrating like it was Christmas all year, which it basically was for them," wrote Frank Clemente, executive director</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>1</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4508538</uri>
        <title>India's tariff to cost US $900m</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.09019607843137256</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Business/International Business and Trade, dmoz/Business/International Business and Trade/Import and Export, dmoz/Society/Issues/Economic</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>64</article_count>
        <total_article_count>64</total_article_count>
        <summary>Washington: India's proposed retaliatory tariffs against US agricultural products including apples, almonds and lentils will have an adverse impact on American exports worth nearly $900 million, according to the latest Congressional report.  India, in 2018, had announced higher import duties on many US products like apples, almonds, walnuts, chickpeas and lentils in retaliation to President Donald Trump's decision to impose heavy tariffs on imported steel and aluminium items, a move that sparked </summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4514562</uri>
        <title>For-Profit Chain Cancels $494 Million in Student Debt to End State Investigations</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.09019607843137245</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Business/Financial Services/College Financing, dmoz/Society/Issues/Education</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>64</article_count>
        <total_article_count>64</total_article_count>
        <summary>Nearly 180,000 former students at for-profit schools run by Career Education will not have to repay $494 million they owed to the company, a group of 49 state attorneys general announced Thursday.  The agreement to wipe out the debt held directly by Career Education, such as unpaid tuition, ended a five-year multistate investigation into complaints that the company used predatory and deceptive recruiting tactics.  Career Education misled students about the cost of its programs and its graduates' </summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4513955</uri>
        <title>Log Cabins? No, These Wooden Buildings Are High-Rises</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1843137254901961</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Business/Construction and Maintenance/Building Types, dmoz/Computers/Software/Build Management, dmoz/Business/Agriculture and Forestry/Forestry</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>7</article_count>
        <total_article_count>7</total_article_count>
        <summary>Developers have not used wood for much other than houses since the horse-and-buggy days. But the knotty building material is making a comeback.  Seeking greener projects, which many consumers continue to embrace despite an anti-environmental mood in Washington, builders are choosing timber for offices, apartments and campus buildings, rather than the concrete and steel that dominated construction for decades.  Not everybody is on board with the trend, which is playing out from coast to coast. Con</summary>
        <nytimes>1</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4506134</uri>
        <title>India remains fastest growing economy ahead of China despite up/downs</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.2549019607843137</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Business/Financial Services, dmoz/Society/Issues/Government Operations, dmoz/Society/Issues/Economic</categories>
        <loc_country>India</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>11</article_count>
        <total_article_count>11</total_article_count>
        <summary>NEW DELHI: India remained ahead of China to retain the tag world's fastest growing large economy withstanding several ups and downs, spike in oil prices and global trade war like situation during 2018. Indian economy's roller-coaster ride during the year gone by was best captured by the GDP growth. In the first quarter of 2018-19 ending June 30, it grew at an impressive 8.2 per cent, after 7.7 per cent in the first three months of the year.  Then it slipped to 7.1 per cent in the next quarter end</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507138</uri>
        <title>Why Modi Government is Amending the Aadhaar Act and What it Means for You</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1450980392156862</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Society/Transgendered/Law, dmoz/Business/Financial Services/Medical Billing, dmoz/Business/Telecommunications/Customer Management</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>38</article_count>
        <total_article_count>42</total_article_count>
        <summary>New Delhi: The Narendra Modi government has introduced a Bill in parliament that propose amendments to various laws that underpin the Aadhaar ecosystem, in a move that comes after a Supreme Court verdict earlier this year curtailed the sprawling nature of India's biometric authentication programme.  The Aadhaar And Other Laws (Amendment) Bill 2018, which was passed by the cabinet two weeks ago and introduced by information technology minister Ravi Shankar Prasad in the Lok Sabha on Wednesday, con</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507927</uri>
        <title>Hyundai flags tough 2019 as US, China demand stays slow</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.06666666666666665</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Home/Consumer Information/Automobiles, dmoz/Business/Marketing and Advertising/Employment, dmoz/Business/Electronics and Electrical/Electromechanical</categories>
        <loc_country>South Korea</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>37</article_count>
        <total_article_count>37</total_article_count>
        <summary>In his first New Year address to employees, group heir apparent Euisun Chung said Hyundai Motor Co and Kia Motors Corp would together launch 13 new or face-lifted models in 2019.  South Korea's Hyundai Motor Group flagged another year of tepid car sales growth on the back of a slow 2018, saying trade protectionism added uncertainty and major markets such as the United States and China remained sluggish.  In his first New Year address to employees, group heir apparent Euisun Chung said Hyundai Mot</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4508459</uri>
        <title>Delivery Boy Who Saved Lives Of 10 People In Mumbai Hospital Fire Gets Rs 1 Lakh As Reward</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.02745098039215677</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Home/Emergency Preparation/Safety, dmoz/Health/Public Health and Safety, dmoz/Health/Public Health and Safety/Emergency Services</categories>
        <loc_country>India</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>6</article_count>
        <total_article_count>6</total_article_count>
        <summary>The brave delivery boy who saved lives of 10 people during the fire accident at Mumbai's ESIC hospital was given a monetary award of Rs One Lakh.  Siddrameshwar Siddharam Humanabade, a food delivery boy pulled off a heroic act saving lives of numerous people at a Mumbai Hospital which was engulfed in flames on December 17, 2018. Labour minister Santosh Gangwar gave him the reward.  Also Read: Food Delivery Boy Jumps Into Mumbai Hospital That Caught Fire To Rescue Ten People  The braveheart saved </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4516577</uri>
        <title>Rajasthan's New Year Gift To Girls Is Sanitary Pad Vending Machines In All Govt Colleges</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.1843137254901961</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Health/Women's Health/Menstruation</categories>
        <loc_country>India</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Asia</loc_continent>
        <article_count>6</article_count>
        <total_article_count>6</total_article_count>
        <summary>In February 2018, former Chief Minister of Rajasthan Vasundhara Raje had announced that sanitary napkins will be provided to women in rural areas.  The announcement was made as part of a new health scheme which will promote menstrual hygiene. PTI had reported that Rs 76 crore was also allotted for this initiative. As the world welcomes 2019, Rajasthan's new scheme will soon become a reality.  Sanitary napkin vending machines will be installed in all 189 government colleges, Times of India reporte</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>1</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>0</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4505520</uri>
        <title>Protesters call on Sudan president to go</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.207843137254902</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Society/Issues, dmoz/Society/Issues/Territorial Disputes, dmoz/Society/Issues/Economic</categories>
        <loc_country>Sudan</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Africa</loc_continent>
        <article_count>145</article_count>
        <total_article_count>159</total_article_count>
        <summary>Hundreds of protesters have gathered in the Sudanese city of Omdurman to call for an end to the nearly 30-year rule of President Omar al-Bashir.  The BBC's Mohamed Osman says security forces have used tear gas against some of the 300 or so demonstrators there.  Sudan has already been rocked by two weeks of sometimes deadly street demonstrations prompted by a rise in the cost of living.  The anti-government protests first erupted in mid-December over inflation.  The price of bread had tripled in s</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4506220</uri>
        <title>FG provides funds to meet ASUU demands</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.09019607843137245</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Society/Work, dmoz/Society/Issues/Labor, dmoz/Society/Work/Labor-Management Relations</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>45</article_count>
        <total_article_count>45</total_article_count>
        <summary>The protracted strike by the Academic Staff Union of Universities (ASUU) may soon to be called off.  Minister of Labour and Employment, Dr. Chris Ngige, who gave the hint in Onitsha, Anambra State said that funds had been provided to meet most of the demands of the union.  He said the Federal Government would make necessary efforts to ensure that the strike comes to an end this January.  According to Ngige, the issues that made ASUU to embark on strike were based on agreement which the union ente</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4507501</uri>
        <title>Killings in Chicago fall 15% from year before</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>0.09019607843137245</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Science/Earth Sciences, dmoz/Science/Earth Sciences/Geophysics, dmoz/Science/Earth Sciences/Geomatics</categories>
        <loc_country>United States</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>Noth America</loc_continent>
        <article_count>6</article_count>
        <total_article_count>6</total_article_count>
        <summary>ILLINOIS Killings in Chicago fall 15% from year before  Preliminary numbers indicate that homicides in Chicago fell by about 100 last year compared with 2017, though the total again eclipsed the number of killings in Los Angeles and New York combined, according to data released Tuesday.  Police in Chicago, the nation's third-largest city, reported 561 homicides between Jan. 1 and Dec. 31, 2018. That compares with 660 homicides in 2017 and more than 770 in 2016, which marked a 19-year high that pu</summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>0</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
    <results>
        <uri>eng-4509569</uri>
        <title>Here are the new 'Dogs of the Dow,' a simple investing strategy that beat the market last year</title>
        <event_date>2019-01-01</event_date>
        <sentiment>-0.03529411764705881</sentiment>
        <categories>news/Business, dmoz/Business/Investing, dmoz/Business/Investing/Stocks and Bonds, dmoz/Business/Investing/Research and Analysis</categories>
        <loc_country>-</loc_country>
        <loc_continent>-</loc_continent>
        <article_count>17</article_count>
        <total_article_count>17</total_article_count>
        <summary>The strategy calls for the purchase of the 10 Dow members with the highest dividend yields.  The "Dogs of the Dow" beat the market in 2018. Now meet the new dogs.  One of Wall Street's classic investing strategies, perhaps the most hands-off one, kept investors relatively safe last year -- if one had bought the 10 highest-yielding stocks in the Dow Jones Industrial Average at the beginning of 2018 and held them all year long, it would have only lost 1.5 percent, versus the Dow's 6 percent annual </summary>
        <nytimes>0</nytimes>
        <indiatimes>0</indiatimes>
        <washingtonpost>1</washingtonpost>
        <usatoday>1</usatoday>
        <chinadaily>0</chinadaily>
    </results>
</events>